<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on アニメ海外反応</title>
    <link>https://anime.syui.cf/categories/english/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on アニメ海外反応</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](//gohugo.io). Theme by [term](https://gitlab.com/syui/hugo-theme-term).</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://anime.syui.cf/categories/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Hundred Daisuke Tamaki · Interview with Mr. Ito Aya! 120% brightness and cherish tenderness</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-hundred-daisuke-tamaki--interview-with-mr.-ito-aya-120-brightness-and-cherish-tenderness</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-hundred-daisuke-tamaki--interview-with-mr.-ito-aya-120-brightness-and-cherish-tenderness</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517027781&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517027781&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Hundred Daisuke Tamaki · Interview with Mr. Ito Aya! 120% brightness and cherish tenderness From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Aya Ito who serves as a hundred places in the fourth round! Starting with the impression of the character I play, I answered questions unique to him.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa Make 120% brightness!  - (Hundred sites) How was your first impression?  One hundred places occasionally, Mr. Itoh (Ito): I thought it was a very big child. Emotions and sorrows are bigger and there are many things that can be many different characters, like a tokens, cleopatra, seven change (lol).  Nevertheless, she is always full of energy and I think that surroundings will get better if these children are nearby. It is a gang attitude based on kindness or compassion that emotions burn out with a feeling of excitement. I thought that such a place is very attractive and I am looking forward to playing.  Tweet share - Have you felt that you did not feel like you?  Ito: Like Tama-chan, I can not do it in front of all the classes, but I think that the place to play something in front of friends who are funny may be similar. I also love things (lol), and such a state of mouth is near.  - On the contrary, what part do you feel that you can not do for myself while you are looking at it?  Ito: For example, even in situations where no one can handle it when deciding class class members, I think Tama will surely be a child to give away. Such a thing, I think that it is really amazing where places where people are likely to take the initiative will also take the initiative. Also, where there is action. Many things Tama-chan has decided for a promise by four people. It is a mood maker and I think he is a very wonderful friend.  Tweet share Tweet share - What kind of things do you take care of when you say such things?  Ito: First of all it is to do it well. I have often played the role of a quiet child until now, so I practiced to get 120% brightness. At the same time, I do not want to be a child of just being energetic, I think that it would be nice to be told that Tama&amp;rsquo;s gentle feelings are on the back of the brightness, as I said earlier.  Tweet share - What is the specific scene that you can feel the tenderness of?  Ito: If it was the third episode of last week, when I first went to Hana&amp;rsquo;s chan&amp;rsquo;s house, Hana got cried. Even then, Tama-chan switches the story in a natural way and in a bright direction, right?  Especially for Hana Hana, I thought that there was something like an older sister. Since I have a scene full of Tamachan &amp;rsquo;s kindness in the episode after this, I think that such a face may be easy to perceive.  - Is there an episode that was impressive at the time of dubbing?  Ito: Director Mr. Akira always makes a lecture by becoming Tama-chan by Taking this kind of feeling by Tama&amp;rsquo;s take instruction. That is very interesting and everyone laughing a lot.  Tweet share Tweet share - That story was also told by Mr. Naganawa (Maria). What was it like to be swayed something?  Ito: Yes, there is &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; In interview with Mr. Naganawa, I think that there was a story about I am sorry, gorilla, but there is more gorillas at that place (laugh). Tama-chan talks about gorillas and imitates, but Mr. Acoustic Director san said, You are a gorilla, you are a gorilla, that shock was told (laugh).  - Are there other recommended scenes in the future?  Ito: Personally I love the episodes of Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko. I am a big fan of those two relationships, but Tama is definitely coming out for two scenes why, The housekeeper saw it! Like (laugh). So, I&amp;rsquo;m watching while suddenly interacting with the two people, I think that the position is close to Tama (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share In case A scene with MV is an ad lib of a voice actor!  - On January 24, OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Singing with 4 main casts was released. It seems that MV was also produced.  Ito: MV recording has been very impressive. Everyone casts Slow Start with a unique air feeling, I think that it seems that four characters of Slow Start seems to be intact. It is warm hearted, but it looks like he&amp;rsquo;s also playing a cacchia. The shooting was a very long time, but it was also a pleasure camp and it was fun.  - Are there any points I would like you to pay attention to with MV?  Ito: There are plenty! First of all, since I love idols, I&amp;rsquo;d like you to pay attention to the scenes I&amp;rsquo;m dancing and I&amp;rsquo;d love to imitate and dance. The rest is a pajamas-like scene that is wearing a room, the director is just doing well and energetic, all the movements are all our ad-libs, so who&amp;rsquo;s where and what I am doing Well, I&amp;rsquo;m happy if you can see it well.  - By the way, Slow Start is a work that depicts the lives of high school students, what kind of high school days did Mr. Ito spent?  Ito: While I was in high school, I was in the chorus section, but that was a serious sports organization-like club activity. Takarazuka was also a big fan at the same time as he was doing his best in the club activities and the days when he was free went through all the time. It was Kyoto, but I often go to Hyogo. Especially at the performance of a favorite person, it is already every weekend. I did not have a part-time job, so my pocket money was gone and it was serious (lol).  Tweet share - What other memories in school life?  Ito: What was that &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; I was pretty fast. Because it was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, there was air that seemed to like it without concern for the boys, and we were with friends every day for about nine people, but everyone was toasting fast (lol).  Tweet share Tweet share - There are many groups of 9 people.  Ito: It was noisy ~ (laugh). I was doing things that seemed to be very high school girls, such as something of a comedian. Also, since I was personally interested in arranging hair, I often played with my friend&amp;rsquo;s hair or making it a maniac hair style. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly how complicated your hair is with her daughter role in Takarazuka. I longed for it, I was like a hair arranger in my friend and I was practicing well.  I would like to make ice with liquid nitrogen! And the question to Mr. Atsumi &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;  - It is the corner of the annual relay question that was followed by the question, but from the last Naganawa (Maria) san, the question What experiment do you want to do?  Ito: It does not have anything to do with it Slow Start (laugh). I wonder what &amp;hellip;. Ah, I want to do that, I make ice cream with liquid nitrogen. Ice is made in a moment by consolidating raw materials. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to a shop selling it before, but it seems to be very interesting and I would like to try it too.  Tweet share - Next will be the authors Atsumi Miko Atsumi Sonoko, but what question would you like to ask?  Ito: There are lots of them &amp;hellip; Well, I like the relationship between Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko, What is Enoki Teacher doing on holiday? Also I would like to know Hobby Enoki Enoki Hobby.  - In the end please give a message to the readers.  Ito: The feeling of the air is relaxed, and there is not a flashy thing about Burn, but when you watch &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; you will notice the small happiness of daily life. I think that such a place is a wonderful work.  Also, watching those four people, I think I want to be with such a wonderful friend, and when I look at the relationship between Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m seeing girls&amp;rsquo; comics. I think that it is a work that can make various ways of enjoying like that, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy if you can see it by various people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Ichinose Hana Nami / Rena Kondo interview! Flower name&#39;s gentle heart is attractive</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-ichinose-hana-nami-/-rena-kondo-interview-flower-names-gentle-heart-is-attractive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-ichinose-hana-nami-/-rena-kondo-interview-flower-names-gentle-heart-is-attractive</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515151972&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515151972&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Ichinose Hana Nami / Rena Kondo interview! Flower name&amp;rsquo;s gentle heart is attractive During serialization at Manga Time Kirara (Yoshifusa), Professor Yuiko Atsumi&amp;rsquo;s popular four-frame manga Slow Start. The same animation will be made into TV animation, broadcasting will start at TOKYO MX and others from January 6, 2018 (Sat). In conjunction with the official website at the animate times, we posted a long version of the series animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview that targets everyone in the main cast and the staff! It is the main character of this work, Mr. Inonose Flower name role, Mr. Rena Kondo who appears in the first memorable occasion! We have answered questions unique to flower name, including the impression of the character who plays.  Tweet share In case Favorite of Hana Kana when I looked up at the cherry tree is my favorite - Can you talk about flower name where Mr. Kondo is played from the first impression first?  Kazuyuki Ichinose (Kondo), Mr. Rena Kondo (Kondo): Hana always has bubbles all the time, she is worried about being a crybaby, and thinking too much about various things, I&amp;rsquo;m really worried about seeing it Although it is a child like that, I thought that it was a very funny child, as he was pretty in the way he was wearing his mind.  Tweet share - What did you feel about the most attractive flower name?  Kondo: It&amp;rsquo;s a rebound idea, but I thought that feelings and thoughts for others are more than one-sided. When I sympathize with something, I sometime cry, I think that a gentle heart that can understand the feeling as if crying is attractive.  - Is there a place you feel like looking at flower names and being similar to yourself?  Kondo: There are many! First of all, when I talk to a person who I met for the first time, I was trying to say things I do not understand (lol).  Also, I do not have the courage to call out even though I want to take pictures with people who co-starred &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Hana has a similar scene, but I thought I&amp;rsquo;m the same as me! (Laugh).  Tweet share - Even on this occasion, have you been rushing like a flower name?  Kondo: There were a lot of them when I was not familiar with it yet. Even if I was spoken to, I was excited and there were quite awkward conversations like Sobo, that&amp;rsquo;s right! (Laugh).  However, as time goes by and the time of four people together with the Nico Nico live broadcasting program, the special location&amp;rsquo;s location or ne! Ne! Ne! Music video shoots, I can gradually put myself out It has become like becoming lol lolly while having fun all day with lately (lol).  - On the contrary, is there anything that you think you can not do with your flower name?  Kondo: I thought that the scene teaching studying to people is amazing. I am not very good at studying and I am very poor at explaining to people. Before it became a different story I was told differently, What are you talking about? Or you said that you do not understand even if you use a metaphor &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Japanese is difficult (lol) . So I can think that Hanami is amazing in double that I can study and explain to people.  - What are the important things to play such a flower name?  Kondo: Since Hana gets to know various worlds really after meeting Tama&amp;rsquo;s and Eiki-chan, crown-chan, it&amp;rsquo;s like being surprised and impressed when you see something like that for the first time I am careful to link it with the feelings of Hana Hana while imagining what it will be like if I encounter it for the first time.  When I am surprised, I often say Eh! Or Awesome, but sometimes it is Wow! Amazing!, When it sounds like Wow &amp;hellip; amazing &amp;hellip; in a loud voice There are also, I also try to play such a kind of variation that I can distinguish.  Tweet share Tweet share Tweet share - Is there anything left in the impression with the acting guidance received at the after-record scene?  Kondo: I have an episode to do a sports test, but since Hana is unable to exercise, there are many scenes that have been hesitated all the time, but the director says You can give out more vigorous voice I, at that time, replying with hurry, yes, while replying, I think I should try acting I played more than ever. I tried various challenging to put out a rough feeling of breath, and to put out a sense of het heft more extensively.  Tweet share - Also in the first episode that the broadcast refrained from, I would like you to pay attention, can you tell me the recommended points?  Kondo: Hana, who is the first episode, just met everyone, just the first high school life has just begun, I&amp;rsquo;m doing a whole thing, but on the contrary it will not be seen any more so it may be valuable I do not think so (laugh). Besides that, sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s cute to show off a smile that is fun with everyone.  What I also thought was really good is the look of Hanabusa when I looked up at the cherry blossoms when I was walking along the cherry blossoms. It&amp;rsquo;s my favorite feeling that The story of Hana&amp;rsquo;s name starts from here!  The first episode is like tea leaves in green tea - On January 24th this month, the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Will be released. Music videos are also included in the video benefits, but what are the points you care about here?  Kondo: Anyway, the songs that these four people are saying It&amp;rsquo;s fun to be with you is a song that you can really imagine, at first it was singing with Hana-chan&amp;rsquo;s consciousness, but Please sing like yourself and sing I imagined the figure that everyone enjoyed and sang happily.  MV was also difficult for me to do dance of rust, but I was struggling hard, but I worked very hard in the dance lesson, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy to see it. Recording was also very long, but everyone was really energetic up to the end and the distance between each other was further reduced, it was a really fun scene.  - It will be a little more private question, but what kind of high school did you mind Kondo himself?  Kondo: I was not good at sports testing (laugh).  Tweet share - In that respect too, it looks like a flower name (laugh).  Kondo: I am happy that I do not have classes, but I can not do much exercise &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. So, I did my best because I could do a little distance only, but after that &amp;hellip; (laugh). Rather, the choir competition was the most burning for each such event.  I like the choral competition very much. It seems like people of society who are working are visible (laugh). After all I think that there are many children who usually feel like singing troubles if it is a high school student, but if those choruses chorus contest is going to be chorus competition, doing something seriously and singing, adult who is different from usual Was the expression looked and it was transmitted? Because my class won the prize, I was very happy.  - In this consecutive interview, we will make a relay question for the next person, but what would you like to ask Mr. Rima (Tomomi) of Yuko Takakura who will appear next?  Kondo: I wonder, what is it all right? Well then, Eiko Asiko likes fashion, so what do you like about what kind of fashion do you like?  Tweet share - In the end, please give me a message to those who watch the broadcast of the first episode from now.  Kondo: I think the first story of Slow Start is like tea leaves in green tea.  - Is it tea leaves &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.?  Kondo: Yes, there is dietary fiber in the tea leaves, but is not the texture of the fiber finely delicate? So when tea is put in, each tea leaf will do various movements. Slow Start is such a swinging pattern of each of the delicate girls is seen, and it also goes inside the same cup. That is the first episode. So first of all I would like to see the first episode and be swallowed by the unique atmosphere of Slow Start.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 Interview with Professor Yuiko Atsumi, original author of TV anime Slow Start! Show off the creative secrets of flower names!</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-interview-with-professor-yuiko-atsumi-original-author-of-tv-anime-slow-start-show-off-the-creative-secrets-of-flower-names</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-interview-with-professor-yuiko-atsumi-original-author-of-tv-anime-slow-start-show-off-the-creative-secrets-of-flower-names</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517542507&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517542507&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 Interview with Professor Yuiko Atsumi, original author of TV anime Slow Start! Show off the creative secrets of flower names!  From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is the original author / Atsumi Hideko who will appear in the fifth time! I came close to the secret of creation, how I created an attractive character.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa □ [4] Hundred Daisen Tainted role · Aya Ito I can hear the name of flower name when drawing manga - How about watching anime currently on air?  Author, Professor Yuko Atsumi (hereinafter referred to as Teruki): The figure that everyone is moving is still cute. When I was calling the flower name, I was particularly cute to move the fingers of my legs with Mojimoji.  I was surprised that the main four people, as well as the classmates, were carefully drawn, and the details included were amazing. It was my heart that Shiki-chan had the most impact but (laugh), I was planning to paint my breasts a lot, but with anime I&amp;rsquo;m moving beyond expectations.  Tweet share Tweet share - What is the cast of?  Tsuneki: You already have each role, are not you? I myself drew manga and I was surprised to hear the dialogue with the voice of Cast. When listening to the audition&amp;rsquo;s tape for the first time, I thought, Which voice is also like flower name &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; I thought, but when I listened to after a long time, only Kondo (Reina) voice could not hear flower name . I realized that Mr. Kondo is becoming a flower name among me.  - Next I will ask about the original. I think that the setting is unique, but from what point did you think of it?  Atsumi: Kirara editor says, I&amp;rsquo;d like you to make the theme and settings exactly, I first thought about starting a story from the state where the main girl had a secret. However, I did not come up with a specific idea, I thought about the story that flower names that migrated to an apartment gathered various things, and the fact that the flower name was an alien actually However, as expected it is going to get stuck. In such circumstances, I was unexpectedly caught up with a setting called Junior High School Ronin.  Tweet share Tweet share - Flower name is also characterized by extremely introverted character.  Tsunemi: Initially it was a child who was more comfortable with the condition and was going to put out poison. But if Editor liked the pretty place of the flower name and thought that If it is still pretty, is it?, I escalated more and more and became weak until then (laugh). For that reason, the element called a trendy person who was at the beginning was supposed to be carried on the shoulder instead of the flower name.  - Momoyo is also an inward character who can communicate with flower name.  Atsuki: Yes. Actually, there are places like flower name and million years who seem to be alone in one person, it is a character born by one setting division. It is a remnant that there is a common point like a ronin. Many years really like the little useless character right now. When she gets bored and becomes a true person, I will go to the university as it is and will not be involved in the story, so I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what to do in the future.  Tweet share Tweet share - How are you doing?  Atsumi: She is a child like my character. It is a character with attachment, it is very easy to move even in the story. I thought that the series is encouraging as long as there are children familiar as I am, and made it appear. Flower name had a delicious feeling because I did not know anything about school, but I do not want to be like that (laugh).  Tweet share - Eiko is an adult-like charm, and it is a combination with a small but cunning crown.  Atsuni: I thought Ms. Ekiko would go out with a crown and put out my hobby as it was. I wanted a hot chicker.  - Just Ekiko, there are parts that are attracted to Professor Enoki Enoshima.  Tsunemi: Initially it was not supposed to be such an expansion at all. Characters naturally move naturally, and Professor Enami also did not intend to engage in the story if originally. In Slow Start we have a unit of figures in the surname of the main children, and if it is a flower name it is Ichinose, if it is Ekiko Tokura. Therefore, it is because the teacher did not have it as a supporting role &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; but when you noticed, Eikiko approached (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share - How is Shi Tenni?  Atsumi: Shimonen may be the most cartoonish character, is not it? In the first episode I wore high school uniforms sometimes simply because I wanted to wear it (laugh), but if I can express that such things are straight-forward, even if I graduate from college It is because I thought that it was good.  Tweet share - Between the original fans, the depiction that the chest was on the frame frame of the frame became a topic.  Atsumi: If you are 4 comic magazines, the state of 1 page 8 frames will continue, which makes it absolutely monotonous. Perhaps the enthusiasm for wanting to protrude as far as possible from there came out.  Slow Start is a story that 4 people get along - Where is the sticking point on the design aspect of the character?  Tsunemi: I was thinking to know who the silhouette is alone, and I especially cared for the hairstyle. The part that connects the hair of flower name is a heart &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;, but recently it seems only to Genji Pie (laugh). It is to make it so that it does not get in the way with the collective painting that made the old ribbon only one side. The twin tail was meant for hair at the beginning, but now I am drawing as if I was like a ribbon. The crown also decided from the beginning to let the ribbon stand like a tactile sense.  Tweet share It is to make it so that it does not get in the way with the collective painting that made the old ribbon only one side. The twin tail was meant for hair at the beginning, but now I am drawing as if I was like a ribbon. The crown also decided from the beginning to let the ribbon stand like a tactile sense.  Tweet share Tweet share Noriko is a character whose design has changed the most. I thought that I would like to draw a character which hair gradually grows, but if I draw it with a habit, my hair became longer and naturally I was able to get a feeling of stretching. Although it was unconscious, it was very good as a result.  Tweet share - The atmosphere in the school is also attractive as being set up for classmates as well, but where is the point in drawing the girls&amp;rsquo; high sense of air?  Atsumi: I myself are from co-school, so I think that I am surely becoming a high-school girl in imagination. I also hear that the actual girls&amp;rsquo; height is different from the imagination unexpectedly (laugh). But I try not to show such a face.  - By the way, what kind of high school days did Mr. Atsumi pass?  Atsuni: Although I wanted to return home as soon as the lesson was over, the teacher was such a person, the chime after school rang and riding a bicycle and beside me, my teacher&amp;rsquo;s car Started running briskly and said, Oh, the teacher wants to go home early too (laugh). I was worried a bit whether I was OK with such an appropriate teacher &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.  - There seems to be a part that communicates with Dr. Enoki Enoki.  Atsumi: Perhaps there are similar parts (laugh). Perhaps the real experience is being reflected before I notice it.  Tweet share - Next is the corner of the relay question, but the question from Mr. Ito (SAZA) in the last time, as a big fan of Mr. Enokon, is How does Enokonaga stay in a holiday? It is.  Atsuki: Hmm &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. It seems to be very dull (laugh). Enoki teacher is actually going to the gym, there are many back settings that are not put out in this volume. And the bed is king size.  Tweet share - Why is that? (Lol) Atsuki: I do not understand either (laugh). Is it because I want to stretch both hands and sleep extensively? That&amp;rsquo;s why I think that holidays are kicking off with a king size bed.  - Next time I will be director of Hashimoto (Hiroyuki), but please ask the question I would like to hear.  Atsuki: That&amp;rsquo;s right &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; If the director were a girl, who would you be the closest to the four? Since the director has been working on works that come up with a lot of pretty girls, I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what kind of child I can most easily emotion.  &amp;ndash;Thank you. Comic 5 volumes were released on January 27. Thank you for your attention.  Atsuki: It is an episode when Ms. Ekiko and the crown were children. In the volume of a sports test of one volume, I painted a crush (Episode of episode 2 in TV animation) that Mr. Ekiko will help the crown solicited to the athletics department, but it is a story like that answer. Eikiko was drawing as a very solid child at the beginning of the series, but this time I could draw her weakness as well. I think that I was good that I could make a human taste Tweet share - The round of the sports test has just been broadcast, and those who knew Slow Start with animation seem to get into the work world smoothly.  Atsumi: That&amp;rsquo;s right. Please enjoy the relationship between the two.  - Please give a message to the readers at the end.  Atsumi: Slow Start is a story that four girls get to know each other little by little. In the original, four of us are deeply friends, but I felt nostalgic when I saw the figure that the flower name still fumbling in animation is doing my best to become friends. Even with animation, we will trust each other as we repeat the conversation, and eventually the flower name will build on irreplaceable relationships. I am happy if you can feel the change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Hashimoto Hiroyuki Director! Publish the story behind the production site!</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-hashimoto-hiroyuki-director-publish-the-story-behind-the-production-site</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-hashimoto-hiroyuki-director-publish-the-story-behind-the-production-site</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1518164769&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1518164769&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Hashimoto Hiroyuki Director! Publish the story behind the production site!  From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. Hiroyuki Hashimoto is the director who will appear in the sixth time. From the launch of the project to the episode of the school days, I got a wide range of stories.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa □ [4] Hundred Daisen Tainted role · Aya Ito □ [Series 5] Author, Professor Yuko Atsumi The quality created by the love of the staff - Please tell me about how the project started.  Director Hashimoto Hiroyuki (Hashimoto): It is a trigger that a producer of Aniplex asked me to animate the original favorite Mr. Hashimoto liked. So first, I started sending a lot of manga and light novels and started reading it. Among them, Slow Start was very interesting.  - Where did you feel charm?  Hashimoto: As the paintings are pretty cute, I was attracted to the place with a little dark part at the same time. The setting that the hero was a junior high school ronin is not an ordinary daily system work, is not it? Although the basic is a bright world view, the surprising aspect of the character is gradually visible. I was fascinated by the sense that such various elements mixed up, and the plan started to animate this original.  Tweet share - Although it is a series of works serialized in Manga Time Kirara, what kind of consultation was made with Mr. Atsumi of the original author?  Hashimoto: Although it is still in the serial series, since animation needs to be summarized in one hour, it asked about the future flow of the original. I also got the profile of the character, but each person had very detailed settings. It is too small so I wonder if it can be reflected in the work (lol).  - Is there anything different about the creation of work by having detailed settings?  Hashimoto: For example, a character that does not like dogs usually does not talk about dogs, right? So the more you know the information, the better you can accumulate depictions of details, the conversation will become more and more natural. For us to visualize, the more information given, the easier it will be.  - How did the main staff decide upon animation?  Hashimoto: From the series, the series composition asked Mr. Inoue (Mio) who has been with us before. Character design Anno (Masato) is an introduction from the production producer of A-1 Pictures.  Mr. Anno came up with a rough design at the stage of not having decided whether to participate yet as soon as a consultation. I thought that it was a great motivation, and moreover, it was a picture that kept the original point, neatly finished as it was to make a decided manuscript.  Tweet share - In animation, the movement of the character is drawn very very attractive, but is it that Mr. Anno&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm is also greatly involved?  Hashimoto: That&amp;rsquo;s really big. Announcer, including Mr. Anno, is touched by the work affectionately. All drawing staff have a clear vision of I want to move this character like this. I want to reflect that enthusiasm on the screen as much as possible. Although Avan of the 1 st story is also working on the original picture, Mr. Yasuno moved it enormously attractively.  Tweet share Tweet share Tweet share - What kind of concept did the director Hashimoto himself face with animation?  Hashimoto: I was conscious of making it possible to see all the stories as much as possible. After all, no matter how hard the drawing works, it will not be rewarded if you can not see it. So I think the director is responsible for creating works that I would like to continue to watch with the first episode, the second episode, the third episode.  - What kind of things is important to keep viewing continued?  Hashimoto: First of all, I kept my mind to not give as much negative image of Junior High School Ronin as possible. In the first episode I also draw a scene that you know that the flower name was a junior high school ronin with a slightly more gentle touch than the original.  There is a voice and music in the big difference between animation and manga. As they enter, the damage to the receiver will also be larger than the manga. So that the flower name is a junior high school student was conveyed by narration at the time of C part where she became a bright expression, so as to ease the shock.  Tweet share Tweet share - I feel that warmth is also in front of the background art.  Hashimoto: In order not to give heavy feeling also, I aimed for cute coloring. Since the school incorporates pastel colors and the walls are pink, the image looks like a kindergarten instead of high school. If I draw a figure standing with a flower name on a brown corridor, it looks somewhere sad. I tried to eliminate such a negative factor.  Is Eiki child oriented for animation director?  - What kind of policy did you decide for casting?  Hashimoto: Four of the main casts decided to be young. For me, Kirara work thinks how deep the main cast&amp;rsquo;s bond is important. Not only in animation but also in sync in realism is cherished, even if it is a young voice actor everyone is easy to match in the event. Some of the fans are looking forward to the casting intersection. I hope something that can not be gained by animation alone will be experienced through casts.  Tweet share Tweet share - How was the after-recording site?  Hashimoto: I thought that you want the character to break a little bit from the cast side. If a play that seems to be surprised comes out as This child has such a voice, a new aspect of the character is born.  By becoming animated from manga, breath is blown into the character by the voice actor. And Mr. Atsumi was influenced by their voices, and the possibilities of the character spread further. If I circulate in a good meaning like that, I am thinking that the work Slow Start will be more enjoyable.  Tweet share - Is there too much ad lib?  Hashimoto: Yes, I think I want to enter if there is a chance, and Cast also has a place that is aiming for ad lib. (Laugh). Ultimately, after dubbing is a sound director (Akutagawa) If Mr. Hitoshi laughs a lot (laugh), if ad lib is interesting and properly matches the world view, it is often adopted as it is. Just like drawing, I value your enthusiasm.  - The series will be in the second half of the game soon. Where&amp;rsquo;s the sights of the future?  Hashimoto: In the second half I will fly more and more. I&amp;rsquo;m worried that the brakes are broken (lol). Especially, Eiko Seki and episodes of Enami are essential. Because something that Mr. Atsumi can not hide is overflowing (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share There are also swimming suit. It was an expansion that seems to be Slow Start that the original does not go to the sea or the pool just by buying a swimwear, but decided to go for a swim in animation. I wanted to complement each other not being drawn with manga, or to give a person who knew the work by animation to get a feeling of being connected to each other, I guess the original is like this.  - Next, it is an annual question in this series, what kind of high school life did Mr. Hashimoto live?  Hashimoto: It was a boys&amp;rsquo; school, and it was nothing special every day (laugh). Just since then I thought that I would like to be an animator. Just when I was a high school student, Kiki&amp;rsquo;s Delivery Service was released, it was interesting and I saw it six times in three days. I bought a byte from there immediately and bought an LD player, and I looked back and forth many times after LD was released.  - Where did you attract Witch&amp;rsquo;s Delivery Service?  Hashimoto: I am from Kyoto, but I wanted to get out to Tokyo earlier from that time. It seems that the story of his own feeling and the story of Kiki going out to the city alone and training is synchronized. I think that there is a part similar to Slow Start, Witch&amp;rsquo;s house. Both are brightly totally, but there are also a few paintings of the painful spots of reality. Because I changed the test, I feel in common where the strength of the heroine is born.  Tweet share - Next is the relay question corner. From last time Mr. Atsumi asked, If the director were a girl, who would you think is the closest among the four? (Laugh).  Hashimoto: Eiko, you&amp;rsquo;re right. I am a de Morono (lol). Ekiko also seems to be inviting a little for classmates, but it seems like S, but suddenly it looks like M in front of Enami. So when I draw Eikiko, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m understanding as if I&amp;rsquo;m doing it happily.  In the first place, the job of an animation director has a place like de M which is troubled by myself while annoying others. I think that I can turn the schedule well if Eikiko becomes the director (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share &amp;ndash;(Lol). Then ask questions to Mr. Inoue of the next series composition.  Hashimoto: If you were a man, whose boyfriend would you like to be? (Laugh). Not from the main 4 people, but from seven people including Enami, &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; Whatever you put in all the classmates (laugh). Mr. Inoue who knew the character as a series composition, it should be able to answer &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; and I tried to demonstrate S ___ 0.  - Please give a message to the reader at the end.  HASHIMOTO: Although Slow Start is a work with many sights, I&amp;rsquo;d like to have fans first enjoy themselves. From my fans, I was pleased that It was good that I became such animation. If I do not do that, animation will not get excited, and I&amp;rsquo;d like others to be proud of so Slow Start was funny from the front! (Laugh). It is my goal to make it work that you can say so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Masaru Naganawa Masaru Naganawa Attractive appearance and personality gap in crown</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-masaru-naganawa-attractive-appearance-and-personality-gap-in-crown</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-masaru-naganawa-attractive-appearance-and-personality-gap-in-crown</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Masaru Naganawa Masaru Naganawa Attractive appearance and personality gap in crown From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside Carefully cherish the feeling that crown really wants to do - Please tell us from the impression when you first saw the crown (Sengoku) first.  Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, How small a child is, really a high school student (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child It became clear.  Tweet share - What do you think is the appeal of such a crown?  Naganawa: After all, is it a gap between appearance and personality? It is also the strength of the core that I said at the moment, although it is very small and it is cute, it is a big eater, it is surprisingly a poisonous tongue (laugh).  - Is there a place where Mr. Naganawa is sympathetic to the crown?  Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;hellip;, but even if I talk about being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.  Tweet share Tweet share - What do you care about playing the crown?  Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of doing things that the crown really wants to do. For example, when it comes to a story like I will give you better things next year about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks Hall cake is good It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).  Tweet share - Is there anything left in the impression on the interaction at the after-recording site? Either Cast or Staff.  Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, This performance is a bit more like this, you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) Welcome to Muku and feel like English? Like Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome to Mom, but it is interesting and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).  Full of feelings to say Sorry, gorilla!  - Have you also had a lecture on the crown?  Naganawa: I did not have much lectures, but I always thought I wanted to be blurred somewhere (laugh). While drinking, I think that it will be slightly different, I am going to put in an awkward ad lib, but mostly it says I do not need (laugh).  But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you Please add ad libs over there and said This foolish people. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought I&amp;rsquo;m happy!  Tweet share - Please let me know the scenes recommended by Ms. Nagana in other main contents.  Naganawa: In the sports test of episode 2, it is a place where a crown is caught and a cool shoulder is presented to a tired Hana name. But, after all, the two people slid down the banks, It was kind of coolly presented out! It was very fun together with the picture.  Tweet share There is a scene in which the crown is I am sorry, gorilla with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say I am sorry, gorilla as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.  - Also next week the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Sung by the main cast will be released on January 24th. Can you explain briefly what kind of song it is?  Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way No, no, no, but here four people have come to say no in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.  If you keep two pets and give it a name &amp;hellip;?  - Here is a question that changed the taste of the question a little, but how was it like when Ms. Naganawa was in high school?  Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard! It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic, so it seems like &amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s do it (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.  Tweet share Tweet share - Er, is that in the school building?  Naganawa: It was a time of rebuilding, it was a prefabricated school building. But everyone was fine just to destroy the prefabricated floor (laugh).  - Next, I want to move to the section of relay question, but from last time Mr. Lingouchi said that he wanted to keep a cat before Mr. Naganawa said If you can keep a pet, I will keep what animal What is your name? Asked What is your name?  Nagano: I&amp;rsquo;m lost ~. A cat, a dog or a bird &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; For now, I will make cats and birds one by one. The type of cat is Munchkin, so its name is astringent &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The name of the pet is thinking when walking well, I do not have any (laugh). That&amp;rsquo;s why I thought about this, Seirin of a cat.  Tweet share Tweet share - Why is it such a Japanese name?  Nagan: What? You do not want twist? When asked, What do you mean cute cat?, What do you think? Wow? Cocoa? No, Mocha? No, I do not know The correct answer is Ki It was Ming!  Well, why did you want it? (Laugh). I want to laugh a lot (laugh).  - I see. (Laugh). So what is the other one?  Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval properly, I will become a scene like I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. Hayato (laugh). Because I want a reaction like Why ~? I know a friend you know.  - So, next question (hundred areas) I&amp;rsquo;d like to ask Aya Ito who is a role for a while.  Nagan: What is it &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; Is it okay if I have nothing to do with the work? What experiment do you want to do? Everything is okay, even if you explore something, even if it explodes (laugh).  Tweet share -(Lol). Please give me a message to the readers at the end.  Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin against it and it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), as everyone&amp;rsquo;s ties deepen, everyone&amp;rsquo;s expression also I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.  In case Work information TV anime Slow Start Broadcast on January 6, 2018 (Tue) on air!  &lt;Broadcast information&gt; TOKYO MX, Taguchi TV, Gunma TV, BS 11: Every Saturday 24: 30 ~ Kansai Television: Every Thursday 26: 25 ~ TV Aichi: Every Tuesday 26: 05 - AT-X: Every Monday 20: 00 ~ ※ Every Wednesday 12: 00 ~ / every Friday 28: 00 ~ repeat broadcasting ※ Broadcast date and time may be changed due to circumstances of organization. Please note.  【Opening theme】 STARTails ☆ (Rena Kondo, Aya Ito, Tomomi Linouchi, Maria Naganawa) no! no! no!  Wednesday, January 24, 2018 released!  【STAFF】 Original: Atsumi Miko (Yoshifusa Manga Time Kirara series) Director: Hiroyuki Hashimoto Series composition: Mio Inoue Character design · total drawing director: Masato Yano Prop Design: Masako Ito Main animator: Yorito Yoshida Art director: Kisen Henibu Color design: Hoka Naka Nako CG Director: Shinji Nasu Director of Photography: Satoshi Kuroiwa Editing Acoustic director: Kawahito Meida Acoustic effect: Toshiya Wada Music: Yoshimasa Fujisawa Music production: Aniplex 制作：A-1 Pictures 【CAST】 Ichinose Hana&amp;rsquo;s name: Rina Kondo One hundred places before: Aya Ito Yuko Takakura: Tomonori Linouchi Sengoku crown: Maria Naganawa Shima Kyotuka: M · A · O Million Year Competition: Wadare Uchida Kiyoshi Enami: Manami Numakura TV anime Slow Start official website TV anime Slow Start Official Twitter (@ slosta_anime) &amp;copy; Atsumi Miko / Yoshifusashi / Slow Start Production Committee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Yuko Takakura role interview with Mr. Tominari Ling Inside! What is the attention scene of the early story for Eiko</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-yuko-takakura-role-interview-with-mr.-tominari-ling-inside-what-is-the-attention-scene-of-the-early-story-for-eiko</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-yuko-takakura-role-interview-with-mr.-tominari-ling-inside-what-is-the-attention-scene-of-the-early-story-for-eiko</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515724499&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515724499&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Yuko Takakura role interview with Mr. Tominari Ling Inside! What is the attention scene of the early story for Eiko From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Tomoko Ryouchi, Ms. Yuko Takura, Mr. Tominori Ling Inside who will appear in the second time! We have answered questions unique to Eiko, including the impression of the character we play.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo In case Eiko is the most ordinary girl in a sense - How was the first impression of Mr. Ekiko (Tokura) being played?  Yuko Takakura, Mr. Tominori Inouchi (hereinafter referred to as Morie): I thought that looks good, I thought it was a light girl with footwork. Indeed, not only the group of flower names but also the children of other groups are good friends, talking about (oh) that things like that (lol). But now I think that it is an interesting child who finds many new aspects as you see it. As the four people get along with each other, there are expressions and dialogue saying This is only for good friends.  Tweet share - What kind of place do you think is such charm of Noriko?  MIYAKI: I think that it is wonderful to have a very girl appearance. From the girls perspective, I think that it is Eiko as many points that I can empathize most. Behavior is not ordinary in many cases (lol), even when talking with others, I often look at the relationship between my friends and give priority to what people want to do rather than what I want to do, as well as family It is surprisingly normal and in some sense it is the most ordinary girl. Even from the viewpoint of men, I think that it is a child who is easy to understand as having a familiar feeling of becoming such a child!  Tweet share Tweet share - Do you feel that you resemble yourself?  Ryoke: In fact, Eikiko actually does not talk much when he&amp;rsquo;s four people. Temporarily speaking the most, about squeezing the mouth occasionally against it. I also like to see things about people, I often see that I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about this person like this rather than talking, I think that such a standing position is very close to me I will.  - On the contrary, where do you feel you can not imitate yourself?  Morie: You can not imitate the height of that communication skill (laugh). Among the works, there is a scene to talk to unknown people and listen to contacts, but I think that such place is not a normal child, it is a superhuman (laugh).  Tweet share - Is such a high school student&amp;rsquo;s departed aspect aware even though it can be played?  Inside: In other words, on the contrary, trying to be careful about not to become an adult too much. Even if it is said that it is a mature girl, I think that it is only a high school student to the last, just an adult compared with a classmate. When I am having fun, I smile like a high school student and I think that there is a certainty that I feel that I am a child after all in front of a citizen ???? or an adult.  &amp;ndash;I see. Have you done anything else to create a role?  Ryoke: Ei Niko has a sister, but since myself is a younger sister, I do not know much of her sister&amp;rsquo;s feelings. So, I remembered what girls around me, what kind of ideas and acts are done by my sister? Recently, I feel that Onee-chan was serious again (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share - Please tell me if there are episodes, etc. that were impressive on the dubbing field.  Inside: After drinking is over, when you lend a ballpoint pen to Mr. Kondo, it is returned in a very natural way saying Eikiko chan! (Laugh). The person himself was surprised, Ah &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Sorry ~, I thought Wow! ~ At that time (laugh).  Conversation with Dr. Enoki Enoki is also an important scene for Eiko - Although the first episode was finally broadcasted the other day, is there a recommended scene at the beginning?  Lingyu: In the second episode, there is a scene where a conversation with Professor Enoki Enoki is drawn for the first time, but I was glad if you could keep it in mind as I played it with great care. In that scene I just do not have any other love conversations about ice, but because important scenes are also packed for Eiko, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a future story to feel the delicate distance and relationship between the two I would like you to pay attention to what the future will change.  Tweet share - Also on January 24, the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Sung by four people will be on sale. Can you explain briefly what kind of song it is?  Lingyu: I&amp;rsquo;m not too energetic, not too grown up, there are places that I feel a bit tricky, but there are energetic places like high school students, I think that it is a song that includes both aspects. I myself consciously thought of how I felt it was Sakaeiko, not to be too harsh, singing calmly.  - MVs sung by four people were also made.  Inside: MV was difficult to dance (laugh). But in the scene where four people gather and dance, there is the feeling of air of the four people who always have a close relationship with Slow Start, I felt it was really nice even if I danced. After that the set is fairly elaborate, especially since the projection mapping of the background is really amazing, I am surprised to see it, I think I can get it!  - Then it will be a little private question, but what kind of high school days did you live by Mr. Lingouchi?  Inside: In the afternoon I was doing a popular app while eating rice with a good boy. So, when I watch the scenes that eat lunch for four people at Slow Start, I think that I was like this every day, I miss it.  Also did the sports test. I do not have physical strength, but I liked the movement and I was good at the ball game, so I became understand ~! To serifs such as Mr. Ekiko&amp;rsquo;s Distance is great but control is good (Laugh).  - In this interview series we have established a relay question section. Last time, Mr. Kondo (Rena) who is the name of a flower has come up with a question saying What fashion do you like about fashionable Noriko who is?  Inside: Fashion? I like the dress very much. I like the shape as I can pat on the top and bottom. My jeans have not got a single suit, the skirt calms down.  Tweet share Tweet share - In addition, it is pin although speaking of Ekiko &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.  Inside: Ah, since I started Slow Start, I have more hairpins than Nico. Until then I did not have almost attached it, but recently even myself, I came to search for something cute hairpin. Even Mr. Atsumi of the original, I got a hairpin that seems to be very proud of her birthday gift, I thought a teacher truly ~, so I would like to add it even at the release event.  - Then, do you have any questions you would like to ask Mr. Naganawa (Maria) who will appear next?  Ridai: That&amp;rsquo;s right &amp;hellip; Well then, since Mr. Naganawa said that he would like to have a cat if she can keep it, What kind of animals do you keep if you can keep a pet, and how do you name it? Oh, the crown has two cats, nagomi and cosmetic, so two animals!  Tweet share - Please give a message to the audience at the end.  Lingyu: Four people have just met yet, but as the talk progresses, the distance feeling of everyone gets closer and the response also changes, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy if everyone talks about such a change in relationship. Since I think that I can not say that my true feelings are not good friends, I hope that you can accumulate among all of us that you are such a child that is actually such a child  , I think that you can see more and more fun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] Slow Start Sengoku Crown Interview with Masaru Naganawa! The appearance and character gap between the crown is attractive</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-slow-start-sengoku-crown-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-the-appearance-and-character-gap-between-the-crown-is-attractive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:26:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-slow-start-sengoku-crown-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-the-appearance-and-character-gap-between-the-crown-is-attractive</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I did not have much lectures, but I always thought I wanted to be blurred somewhere (laugh). While drinking, I think that it will be slightly different, I am going to put in an awkward ad lib, but mostly it says &amp;lsquo;I do not need&amp;rsquo; (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: In the sports test of episode 2, it is a place where a crown is &amp;lsquo;caught&amp;rsquo; and a cool shoulder is presented to a tired Hana name. But, after all, the two people slid down the banks, &amp;lsquo;It was kind of coolly presented out!&amp;rsquo; It was very fun together with the picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next I would like to move to the relay question section, but from last time Mr. Lingouchi said that he wanted to keep a cat before Ms. Naganawa said &amp;lsquo;If you can keep a pet, I will keep what animal What is your name? &amp;lsquo;Asked&amp;rsquo; What is your name? &amp;lsquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagano: I&amp;rsquo;m lost ~. A cat, a dog or a bird &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; For now, I will make cats and birds one by one. The type of cat is Munchkin, so its name is astringent &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The name of the pet is thinking when walking well, I have not kept it (laugh). That&amp;rsquo;s why I thought about this, &amp;lsquo;Seirin&amp;rsquo; of a cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: What? You do not want twist? When asked, &amp;lsquo;What do you mean cute cat?&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;What do you think?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Wow? Cocoa?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Mocha?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I do not know&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;The correct answer is Ki It was Ming! &amp;ldquo; Well, why did you want it? &amp;lsquo;(Laugh). I want to laugh a lot (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] Slow Start Sengoku Crown Interview with Masaru Naganawa! The appearance and character gap between the crown is attractive</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/01/23/animatetimes_1516333521_slowstart</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2018 04:40:02 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/01/23/animatetimes_1516333521_slowstart</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I did not have much lectures, but I always thought I wanted to be blurred somewhere (laugh). While drinking, I think that it will be slightly different, I am going to put in an awkward ad lib, but mostly it says &amp;lsquo;I do not need&amp;rsquo; (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: In the sports test of episode 2, it is a place where a crown is &amp;lsquo;caught&amp;rsquo; and a cool shoulder is presented to a tired Hana name. But, after all, the two people slid down the banks, &amp;lsquo;It was kind of coolly presented out!&amp;rsquo; It was very fun together with the picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next I would like to move to the relay question section, but from last time Mr. Lingouchi said that he wanted to keep a cat before Ms. Naganawa said &amp;lsquo;If you can keep a pet, I will keep what animal What is your name? &amp;lsquo;Asked&amp;rsquo; What is your name? &amp;lsquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagano: I&amp;rsquo;m lost ~. A cat, a dog or a bird &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; For now, I will make cats and birds one by one. The type of cat is Munchkin, so its name is astringent &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The name of the pet is thinking when walking well, I have not kept it (laugh). That&amp;rsquo;s why I thought about this, &amp;lsquo;Seirin&amp;rsquo; of a cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: What? You do not want twist? When asked, &amp;lsquo;What do you mean cute cat?&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;What do you think?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Wow? Cocoa?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Mocha?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I do not know&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;The correct answer is Ki It was Ming! &amp;ldquo; Well, why did you want it? &amp;lsquo;(Laugh). I want to laugh a lot (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>