<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Toaru Majutsu no Index Endymion no Kiseki on アニメ海外反応</title>
    <link>https://anime.syui.cf/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toaru Majutsu no Index Endymion no Kiseki on アニメ海外反応</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ja-jp</language>
    <copyright>Powered by [Hugo](//gohugo.io). Theme by [term](https://gitlab.com/syui/hugo-theme-term).</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://anime.syui.cf/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Hundred Daisuke Tamaki · Interview with Mr. Ito Aya! 120% brightness and cherish tenderness</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-hundred-daisuke-tamaki--interview-with-mr.-ito-aya-120-brightness-and-cherish-tenderness</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-hundred-daisuke-tamaki--interview-with-mr.-ito-aya-120-brightness-and-cherish-tenderness</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517027781&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517027781&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Hundred Daisuke Tamaki · Interview with Mr. Ito Aya! 120% brightness and cherish tenderness From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Aya Ito who serves as a hundred places in the fourth round! Starting with the impression of the character I play, I answered questions unique to him.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa Make 120% brightness!  - (Hundred sites) How was your first impression?  One hundred places occasionally, Mr. Itoh (Ito): I thought it was a very big child. Emotions and sorrows are bigger and there are many things that can be many different characters, like a tokens, cleopatra, seven change (lol).  Nevertheless, she is always full of energy and I think that surroundings will get better if these children are nearby. It is a gang attitude based on kindness or compassion that emotions burn out with a feeling of excitement. I thought that such a place is very attractive and I am looking forward to playing.  Tweet share - Have you felt that you did not feel like you?  Ito: Like Tama-chan, I can not do it in front of all the classes, but I think that the place to play something in front of friends who are funny may be similar. I also love things (lol), and such a state of mouth is near.  - On the contrary, what part do you feel that you can not do for myself while you are looking at it?  Ito: For example, even in situations where no one can handle it when deciding class class members, I think Tama will surely be a child to give away. Such a thing, I think that it is really amazing where places where people are likely to take the initiative will also take the initiative. Also, where there is action. Many things Tama-chan has decided for a promise by four people. It is a mood maker and I think he is a very wonderful friend.  Tweet share Tweet share - What kind of things do you take care of when you say such things?  Ito: First of all it is to do it well. I have often played the role of a quiet child until now, so I practiced to get 120% brightness. At the same time, I do not want to be a child of just being energetic, I think that it would be nice to be told that Tama&amp;rsquo;s gentle feelings are on the back of the brightness, as I said earlier.  Tweet share - What is the specific scene that you can feel the tenderness of?  Ito: If it was the third episode of last week, when I first went to Hana&amp;rsquo;s chan&amp;rsquo;s house, Hana got cried. Even then, Tama-chan switches the story in a natural way and in a bright direction, right?  Especially for Hana Hana, I thought that there was something like an older sister. Since I have a scene full of Tamachan &amp;rsquo;s kindness in the episode after this, I think that such a face may be easy to perceive.  - Is there an episode that was impressive at the time of dubbing?  Ito: Director Mr. Akira always makes a lecture by becoming Tama-chan by Taking this kind of feeling by Tama&amp;rsquo;s take instruction. That is very interesting and everyone laughing a lot.  Tweet share Tweet share - That story was also told by Mr. Naganawa (Maria). What was it like to be swayed something?  Ito: Yes, there is &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; In interview with Mr. Naganawa, I think that there was a story about I am sorry, gorilla, but there is more gorillas at that place (laugh). Tama-chan talks about gorillas and imitates, but Mr. Acoustic Director san said, You are a gorilla, you are a gorilla, that shock was told (laugh).  - Are there other recommended scenes in the future?  Ito: Personally I love the episodes of Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko. I am a big fan of those two relationships, but Tama is definitely coming out for two scenes why, The housekeeper saw it! Like (laugh). So, I&amp;rsquo;m watching while suddenly interacting with the two people, I think that the position is close to Tama (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share In case A scene with MV is an ad lib of a voice actor!  - On January 24, OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Singing with 4 main casts was released. It seems that MV was also produced.  Ito: MV recording has been very impressive. Everyone casts Slow Start with a unique air feeling, I think that it seems that four characters of Slow Start seems to be intact. It is warm hearted, but it looks like he&amp;rsquo;s also playing a cacchia. The shooting was a very long time, but it was also a pleasure camp and it was fun.  - Are there any points I would like you to pay attention to with MV?  Ito: There are plenty! First of all, since I love idols, I&amp;rsquo;d like you to pay attention to the scenes I&amp;rsquo;m dancing and I&amp;rsquo;d love to imitate and dance. The rest is a pajamas-like scene that is wearing a room, the director is just doing well and energetic, all the movements are all our ad-libs, so who&amp;rsquo;s where and what I am doing Well, I&amp;rsquo;m happy if you can see it well.  - By the way, Slow Start is a work that depicts the lives of high school students, what kind of high school days did Mr. Ito spent?  Ito: While I was in high school, I was in the chorus section, but that was a serious sports organization-like club activity. Takarazuka was also a big fan at the same time as he was doing his best in the club activities and the days when he was free went through all the time. It was Kyoto, but I often go to Hyogo. Especially at the performance of a favorite person, it is already every weekend. I did not have a part-time job, so my pocket money was gone and it was serious (lol).  Tweet share - What other memories in school life?  Ito: What was that &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; I was pretty fast. Because it was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, there was air that seemed to like it without concern for the boys, and we were with friends every day for about nine people, but everyone was toasting fast (lol).  Tweet share Tweet share - There are many groups of 9 people.  Ito: It was noisy ~ (laugh). I was doing things that seemed to be very high school girls, such as something of a comedian. Also, since I was personally interested in arranging hair, I often played with my friend&amp;rsquo;s hair or making it a maniac hair style. That&amp;rsquo;s exactly how complicated your hair is with her daughter role in Takarazuka. I longed for it, I was like a hair arranger in my friend and I was practicing well.  I would like to make ice with liquid nitrogen! And the question to Mr. Atsumi &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;  - It is the corner of the annual relay question that was followed by the question, but from the last Naganawa (Maria) san, the question What experiment do you want to do?  Ito: It does not have anything to do with it Slow Start (laugh). I wonder what &amp;hellip;. Ah, I want to do that, I make ice cream with liquid nitrogen. Ice is made in a moment by consolidating raw materials. I&amp;rsquo;ve been to a shop selling it before, but it seems to be very interesting and I would like to try it too.  Tweet share - Next will be the authors Atsumi Miko Atsumi Sonoko, but what question would you like to ask?  Ito: There are lots of them &amp;hellip; Well, I like the relationship between Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko, What is Enoki Teacher doing on holiday? Also I would like to know Hobby Enoki Enoki Hobby.  - In the end please give a message to the readers.  Ito: The feeling of the air is relaxed, and there is not a flashy thing about Burn, but when you watch &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; you will notice the small happiness of daily life. I think that such a place is a wonderful work.  Also, watching those four people, I think I want to be with such a wonderful friend, and when I look at the relationship between Professor Enami and Ms. Ekiko, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m seeing girls&amp;rsquo; comics. I think that it is a work that can make various ways of enjoying like that, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy if you can see it by various people.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Ichinose Hana Nami / Rena Kondo interview! Flower name&#39;s gentle heart is attractive</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-ichinose-hana-nami-/-rena-kondo-interview-flower-names-gentle-heart-is-attractive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-serial-tv-anime-slow-start-ichinose-hana-nami-/-rena-kondo-interview-flower-names-gentle-heart-is-attractive</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515151972&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515151972&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Serial】 TV anime Slow Start Ichinose Hana Nami / Rena Kondo interview! Flower name&amp;rsquo;s gentle heart is attractive During serialization at Manga Time Kirara (Yoshifusa), Professor Yuiko Atsumi&amp;rsquo;s popular four-frame manga Slow Start. The same animation will be made into TV animation, broadcasting will start at TOKYO MX and others from January 6, 2018 (Sat). In conjunction with the official website at the animate times, we posted a long version of the series animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview that targets everyone in the main cast and the staff! It is the main character of this work, Mr. Inonose Flower name role, Mr. Rena Kondo who appears in the first memorable occasion! We have answered questions unique to flower name, including the impression of the character who plays.  Tweet share In case Favorite of Hana Kana when I looked up at the cherry tree is my favorite - Can you talk about flower name where Mr. Kondo is played from the first impression first?  Kazuyuki Ichinose (Kondo), Mr. Rena Kondo (Kondo): Hana always has bubbles all the time, she is worried about being a crybaby, and thinking too much about various things, I&amp;rsquo;m really worried about seeing it Although it is a child like that, I thought that it was a very funny child, as he was pretty in the way he was wearing his mind.  Tweet share - What did you feel about the most attractive flower name?  Kondo: It&amp;rsquo;s a rebound idea, but I thought that feelings and thoughts for others are more than one-sided. When I sympathize with something, I sometime cry, I think that a gentle heart that can understand the feeling as if crying is attractive.  - Is there a place you feel like looking at flower names and being similar to yourself?  Kondo: There are many! First of all, when I talk to a person who I met for the first time, I was trying to say things I do not understand (lol).  Also, I do not have the courage to call out even though I want to take pictures with people who co-starred &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Hana has a similar scene, but I thought I&amp;rsquo;m the same as me! (Laugh).  Tweet share - Even on this occasion, have you been rushing like a flower name?  Kondo: There were a lot of them when I was not familiar with it yet. Even if I was spoken to, I was excited and there were quite awkward conversations like Sobo, that&amp;rsquo;s right! (Laugh).  However, as time goes by and the time of four people together with the Nico Nico live broadcasting program, the special location&amp;rsquo;s location or ne! Ne! Ne! Music video shoots, I can gradually put myself out It has become like becoming lol lolly while having fun all day with lately (lol).  - On the contrary, is there anything that you think you can not do with your flower name?  Kondo: I thought that the scene teaching studying to people is amazing. I am not very good at studying and I am very poor at explaining to people. Before it became a different story I was told differently, What are you talking about? Or you said that you do not understand even if you use a metaphor &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Japanese is difficult (lol) . So I can think that Hanami is amazing in double that I can study and explain to people.  - What are the important things to play such a flower name?  Kondo: Since Hana gets to know various worlds really after meeting Tama&amp;rsquo;s and Eiki-chan, crown-chan, it&amp;rsquo;s like being surprised and impressed when you see something like that for the first time I am careful to link it with the feelings of Hana Hana while imagining what it will be like if I encounter it for the first time.  When I am surprised, I often say Eh! Or Awesome, but sometimes it is Wow! Amazing!, When it sounds like Wow &amp;hellip; amazing &amp;hellip; in a loud voice There are also, I also try to play such a kind of variation that I can distinguish.  Tweet share Tweet share Tweet share - Is there anything left in the impression with the acting guidance received at the after-record scene?  Kondo: I have an episode to do a sports test, but since Hana is unable to exercise, there are many scenes that have been hesitated all the time, but the director says You can give out more vigorous voice I, at that time, replying with hurry, yes, while replying, I think I should try acting I played more than ever. I tried various challenging to put out a rough feeling of breath, and to put out a sense of het heft more extensively.  Tweet share - Also in the first episode that the broadcast refrained from, I would like you to pay attention, can you tell me the recommended points?  Kondo: Hana, who is the first episode, just met everyone, just the first high school life has just begun, I&amp;rsquo;m doing a whole thing, but on the contrary it will not be seen any more so it may be valuable I do not think so (laugh). Besides that, sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s cute to show off a smile that is fun with everyone.  What I also thought was really good is the look of Hanabusa when I looked up at the cherry blossoms when I was walking along the cherry blossoms. It&amp;rsquo;s my favorite feeling that The story of Hana&amp;rsquo;s name starts from here!  The first episode is like tea leaves in green tea - On January 24th this month, the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Will be released. Music videos are also included in the video benefits, but what are the points you care about here?  Kondo: Anyway, the songs that these four people are saying It&amp;rsquo;s fun to be with you is a song that you can really imagine, at first it was singing with Hana-chan&amp;rsquo;s consciousness, but Please sing like yourself and sing I imagined the figure that everyone enjoyed and sang happily.  MV was also difficult for me to do dance of rust, but I was struggling hard, but I worked very hard in the dance lesson, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy to see it. Recording was also very long, but everyone was really energetic up to the end and the distance between each other was further reduced, it was a really fun scene.  - It will be a little more private question, but what kind of high school did you mind Kondo himself?  Kondo: I was not good at sports testing (laugh).  Tweet share - In that respect too, it looks like a flower name (laugh).  Kondo: I am happy that I do not have classes, but I can not do much exercise &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. So, I did my best because I could do a little distance only, but after that &amp;hellip; (laugh). Rather, the choir competition was the most burning for each such event.  I like the choral competition very much. It seems like people of society who are working are visible (laugh). After all I think that there are many children who usually feel like singing troubles if it is a high school student, but if those choruses chorus contest is going to be chorus competition, doing something seriously and singing, adult who is different from usual Was the expression looked and it was transmitted? Because my class won the prize, I was very happy.  - In this consecutive interview, we will make a relay question for the next person, but what would you like to ask Mr. Rima (Tomomi) of Yuko Takakura who will appear next?  Kondo: I wonder, what is it all right? Well then, Eiko Asiko likes fashion, so what do you like about what kind of fashion do you like?  Tweet share - In the end, please give me a message to those who watch the broadcast of the first episode from now.  Kondo: I think the first story of Slow Start is like tea leaves in green tea.  - Is it tea leaves &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.?  Kondo: Yes, there is dietary fiber in the tea leaves, but is not the texture of the fiber finely delicate? So when tea is put in, each tea leaf will do various movements. Slow Start is such a swinging pattern of each of the delicate girls is seen, and it also goes inside the same cup. That is the first episode. So first of all I would like to see the first episode and be swallowed by the unique atmosphere of Slow Start.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 Interview with Professor Yuiko Atsumi, original author of TV anime Slow Start! Show off the creative secrets of flower names!</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-interview-with-professor-yuiko-atsumi-original-author-of-tv-anime-slow-start-show-off-the-creative-secrets-of-flower-names</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-interview-with-professor-yuiko-atsumi-original-author-of-tv-anime-slow-start-show-off-the-creative-secrets-of-flower-names</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517542507&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1517542507&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 Interview with Professor Yuiko Atsumi, original author of TV anime Slow Start! Show off the creative secrets of flower names!  From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is the original author / Atsumi Hideko who will appear in the fifth time! I came close to the secret of creation, how I created an attractive character.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa □ [4] Hundred Daisen Tainted role · Aya Ito I can hear the name of flower name when drawing manga - How about watching anime currently on air?  Author, Professor Yuko Atsumi (hereinafter referred to as Teruki): The figure that everyone is moving is still cute. When I was calling the flower name, I was particularly cute to move the fingers of my legs with Mojimoji.  I was surprised that the main four people, as well as the classmates, were carefully drawn, and the details included were amazing. It was my heart that Shiki-chan had the most impact but (laugh), I was planning to paint my breasts a lot, but with anime I&amp;rsquo;m moving beyond expectations.  Tweet share Tweet share - What is the cast of?  Tsuneki: You already have each role, are not you? I myself drew manga and I was surprised to hear the dialogue with the voice of Cast. When listening to the audition&amp;rsquo;s tape for the first time, I thought, Which voice is also like flower name &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; I thought, but when I listened to after a long time, only Kondo (Reina) voice could not hear flower name . I realized that Mr. Kondo is becoming a flower name among me.  - Next I will ask about the original. I think that the setting is unique, but from what point did you think of it?  Atsumi: Kirara editor says, I&amp;rsquo;d like you to make the theme and settings exactly, I first thought about starting a story from the state where the main girl had a secret. However, I did not come up with a specific idea, I thought about the story that flower names that migrated to an apartment gathered various things, and the fact that the flower name was an alien actually However, as expected it is going to get stuck. In such circumstances, I was unexpectedly caught up with a setting called Junior High School Ronin.  Tweet share Tweet share - Flower name is also characterized by extremely introverted character.  Tsunemi: Initially it was a child who was more comfortable with the condition and was going to put out poison. But if Editor liked the pretty place of the flower name and thought that If it is still pretty, is it?, I escalated more and more and became weak until then (laugh). For that reason, the element called a trendy person who was at the beginning was supposed to be carried on the shoulder instead of the flower name.  - Momoyo is also an inward character who can communicate with flower name.  Atsuki: Yes. Actually, there are places like flower name and million years who seem to be alone in one person, it is a character born by one setting division. It is a remnant that there is a common point like a ronin. Many years really like the little useless character right now. When she gets bored and becomes a true person, I will go to the university as it is and will not be involved in the story, so I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what to do in the future.  Tweet share Tweet share - How are you doing?  Atsumi: She is a child like my character. It is a character with attachment, it is very easy to move even in the story. I thought that the series is encouraging as long as there are children familiar as I am, and made it appear. Flower name had a delicious feeling because I did not know anything about school, but I do not want to be like that (laugh).  Tweet share - Eiko is an adult-like charm, and it is a combination with a small but cunning crown.  Atsuni: I thought Ms. Ekiko would go out with a crown and put out my hobby as it was. I wanted a hot chicker.  - Just Ekiko, there are parts that are attracted to Professor Enoki Enoshima.  Tsunemi: Initially it was not supposed to be such an expansion at all. Characters naturally move naturally, and Professor Enami also did not intend to engage in the story if originally. In Slow Start we have a unit of figures in the surname of the main children, and if it is a flower name it is Ichinose, if it is Ekiko Tokura. Therefore, it is because the teacher did not have it as a supporting role &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; but when you noticed, Eikiko approached (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share - How is Shi Tenni?  Atsumi: Shimonen may be the most cartoonish character, is not it? In the first episode I wore high school uniforms sometimes simply because I wanted to wear it (laugh), but if I can express that such things are straight-forward, even if I graduate from college It is because I thought that it was good.  Tweet share - Between the original fans, the depiction that the chest was on the frame frame of the frame became a topic.  Atsumi: If you are 4 comic magazines, the state of 1 page 8 frames will continue, which makes it absolutely monotonous. Perhaps the enthusiasm for wanting to protrude as far as possible from there came out.  Slow Start is a story that 4 people get along - Where is the sticking point on the design aspect of the character?  Tsunemi: I was thinking to know who the silhouette is alone, and I especially cared for the hairstyle. The part that connects the hair of flower name is a heart &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;, but recently it seems only to Genji Pie (laugh). It is to make it so that it does not get in the way with the collective painting that made the old ribbon only one side. The twin tail was meant for hair at the beginning, but now I am drawing as if I was like a ribbon. The crown also decided from the beginning to let the ribbon stand like a tactile sense.  Tweet share It is to make it so that it does not get in the way with the collective painting that made the old ribbon only one side. The twin tail was meant for hair at the beginning, but now I am drawing as if I was like a ribbon. The crown also decided from the beginning to let the ribbon stand like a tactile sense.  Tweet share Tweet share Noriko is a character whose design has changed the most. I thought that I would like to draw a character which hair gradually grows, but if I draw it with a habit, my hair became longer and naturally I was able to get a feeling of stretching. Although it was unconscious, it was very good as a result.  Tweet share - The atmosphere in the school is also attractive as being set up for classmates as well, but where is the point in drawing the girls&amp;rsquo; high sense of air?  Atsumi: I myself are from co-school, so I think that I am surely becoming a high-school girl in imagination. I also hear that the actual girls&amp;rsquo; height is different from the imagination unexpectedly (laugh). But I try not to show such a face.  - By the way, what kind of high school days did Mr. Atsumi pass?  Atsuni: Although I wanted to return home as soon as the lesson was over, the teacher was such a person, the chime after school rang and riding a bicycle and beside me, my teacher&amp;rsquo;s car Started running briskly and said, Oh, the teacher wants to go home early too (laugh). I was worried a bit whether I was OK with such an appropriate teacher &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.  - There seems to be a part that communicates with Dr. Enoki Enoki.  Atsumi: Perhaps there are similar parts (laugh). Perhaps the real experience is being reflected before I notice it.  Tweet share - Next is the corner of the relay question, but the question from Mr. Ito (SAZA) in the last time, as a big fan of Mr. Enokon, is How does Enokonaga stay in a holiday? It is.  Atsuki: Hmm &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. It seems to be very dull (laugh). Enoki teacher is actually going to the gym, there are many back settings that are not put out in this volume. And the bed is king size.  Tweet share - Why is that? (Lol) Atsuki: I do not understand either (laugh). Is it because I want to stretch both hands and sleep extensively? That&amp;rsquo;s why I think that holidays are kicking off with a king size bed.  - Next time I will be director of Hashimoto (Hiroyuki), but please ask the question I would like to hear.  Atsuki: That&amp;rsquo;s right &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; If the director were a girl, who would you be the closest to the four? Since the director has been working on works that come up with a lot of pretty girls, I&amp;rsquo;m worried about what kind of child I can most easily emotion.  &amp;ndash;Thank you. Comic 5 volumes were released on January 27. Thank you for your attention.  Atsuki: It is an episode when Ms. Ekiko and the crown were children. In the volume of a sports test of one volume, I painted a crush (Episode of episode 2 in TV animation) that Mr. Ekiko will help the crown solicited to the athletics department, but it is a story like that answer. Eikiko was drawing as a very solid child at the beginning of the series, but this time I could draw her weakness as well. I think that I was good that I could make a human taste Tweet share - The round of the sports test has just been broadcast, and those who knew Slow Start with animation seem to get into the work world smoothly.  Atsumi: That&amp;rsquo;s right. Please enjoy the relationship between the two.  - Please give a message to the readers at the end.  Atsumi: Slow Start is a story that four girls get to know each other little by little. In the original, four of us are deeply friends, but I felt nostalgic when I saw the figure that the flower name still fumbling in animation is doing my best to become friends. Even with animation, we will trust each other as we repeat the conversation, and eventually the flower name will build on irreplaceable relationships. I am happy if you can feel the change.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Hashimoto Hiroyuki Director! Publish the story behind the production site!</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-hashimoto-hiroyuki-director-publish-the-story-behind-the-production-site</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-hashimoto-hiroyuki-director-publish-the-story-behind-the-production-site</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1518164769&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1518164769&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Hashimoto Hiroyuki Director! Publish the story behind the production site!  From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. Hiroyuki Hashimoto is the director who will appear in the sixth time. From the launch of the project to the episode of the school days, I got a wide range of stories.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside □ 【Series 3】 Mr. Tadashi Sengoku · Mari Naganawa □ [4] Hundred Daisen Tainted role · Aya Ito □ [Series 5] Author, Professor Yuko Atsumi The quality created by the love of the staff - Please tell me about how the project started.  Director Hashimoto Hiroyuki (Hashimoto): It is a trigger that a producer of Aniplex asked me to animate the original favorite Mr. Hashimoto liked. So first, I started sending a lot of manga and light novels and started reading it. Among them, Slow Start was very interesting.  - Where did you feel charm?  Hashimoto: As the paintings are pretty cute, I was attracted to the place with a little dark part at the same time. The setting that the hero was a junior high school ronin is not an ordinary daily system work, is not it? Although the basic is a bright world view, the surprising aspect of the character is gradually visible. I was fascinated by the sense that such various elements mixed up, and the plan started to animate this original.  Tweet share - Although it is a series of works serialized in Manga Time Kirara, what kind of consultation was made with Mr. Atsumi of the original author?  Hashimoto: Although it is still in the serial series, since animation needs to be summarized in one hour, it asked about the future flow of the original. I also got the profile of the character, but each person had very detailed settings. It is too small so I wonder if it can be reflected in the work (lol).  - Is there anything different about the creation of work by having detailed settings?  Hashimoto: For example, a character that does not like dogs usually does not talk about dogs, right? So the more you know the information, the better you can accumulate depictions of details, the conversation will become more and more natural. For us to visualize, the more information given, the easier it will be.  - How did the main staff decide upon animation?  Hashimoto: From the series, the series composition asked Mr. Inoue (Mio) who has been with us before. Character design Anno (Masato) is an introduction from the production producer of A-1 Pictures.  Mr. Anno came up with a rough design at the stage of not having decided whether to participate yet as soon as a consultation. I thought that it was a great motivation, and moreover, it was a picture that kept the original point, neatly finished as it was to make a decided manuscript.  Tweet share - In animation, the movement of the character is drawn very very attractive, but is it that Mr. Anno&amp;rsquo;s enthusiasm is also greatly involved?  Hashimoto: That&amp;rsquo;s really big. Announcer, including Mr. Anno, is touched by the work affectionately. All drawing staff have a clear vision of I want to move this character like this. I want to reflect that enthusiasm on the screen as much as possible. Although Avan of the 1 st story is also working on the original picture, Mr. Yasuno moved it enormously attractively.  Tweet share Tweet share Tweet share - What kind of concept did the director Hashimoto himself face with animation?  Hashimoto: I was conscious of making it possible to see all the stories as much as possible. After all, no matter how hard the drawing works, it will not be rewarded if you can not see it. So I think the director is responsible for creating works that I would like to continue to watch with the first episode, the second episode, the third episode.  - What kind of things is important to keep viewing continued?  Hashimoto: First of all, I kept my mind to not give as much negative image of Junior High School Ronin as possible. In the first episode I also draw a scene that you know that the flower name was a junior high school ronin with a slightly more gentle touch than the original.  There is a voice and music in the big difference between animation and manga. As they enter, the damage to the receiver will also be larger than the manga. So that the flower name is a junior high school student was conveyed by narration at the time of C part where she became a bright expression, so as to ease the shock.  Tweet share Tweet share - I feel that warmth is also in front of the background art.  Hashimoto: In order not to give heavy feeling also, I aimed for cute coloring. Since the school incorporates pastel colors and the walls are pink, the image looks like a kindergarten instead of high school. If I draw a figure standing with a flower name on a brown corridor, it looks somewhere sad. I tried to eliminate such a negative factor.  Is Eiki child oriented for animation director?  - What kind of policy did you decide for casting?  Hashimoto: Four of the main casts decided to be young. For me, Kirara work thinks how deep the main cast&amp;rsquo;s bond is important. Not only in animation but also in sync in realism is cherished, even if it is a young voice actor everyone is easy to match in the event. Some of the fans are looking forward to the casting intersection. I hope something that can not be gained by animation alone will be experienced through casts.  Tweet share Tweet share - How was the after-recording site?  Hashimoto: I thought that you want the character to break a little bit from the cast side. If a play that seems to be surprised comes out as This child has such a voice, a new aspect of the character is born.  By becoming animated from manga, breath is blown into the character by the voice actor. And Mr. Atsumi was influenced by their voices, and the possibilities of the character spread further. If I circulate in a good meaning like that, I am thinking that the work Slow Start will be more enjoyable.  Tweet share - Is there too much ad lib?  Hashimoto: Yes, I think I want to enter if there is a chance, and Cast also has a place that is aiming for ad lib. (Laugh). Ultimately, after dubbing is a sound director (Akutagawa) If Mr. Hitoshi laughs a lot (laugh), if ad lib is interesting and properly matches the world view, it is often adopted as it is. Just like drawing, I value your enthusiasm.  - The series will be in the second half of the game soon. Where&amp;rsquo;s the sights of the future?  Hashimoto: In the second half I will fly more and more. I&amp;rsquo;m worried that the brakes are broken (lol). Especially, Eiko Seki and episodes of Enami are essential. Because something that Mr. Atsumi can not hide is overflowing (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share There are also swimming suit. It was an expansion that seems to be Slow Start that the original does not go to the sea or the pool just by buying a swimwear, but decided to go for a swim in animation. I wanted to complement each other not being drawn with manga, or to give a person who knew the work by animation to get a feeling of being connected to each other, I guess the original is like this.  - Next, it is an annual question in this series, what kind of high school life did Mr. Hashimoto live?  Hashimoto: It was a boys&amp;rsquo; school, and it was nothing special every day (laugh). Just since then I thought that I would like to be an animator. Just when I was a high school student, Kiki&amp;rsquo;s Delivery Service was released, it was interesting and I saw it six times in three days. I bought a byte from there immediately and bought an LD player, and I looked back and forth many times after LD was released.  - Where did you attract Witch&amp;rsquo;s Delivery Service?  Hashimoto: I am from Kyoto, but I wanted to get out to Tokyo earlier from that time. It seems that the story of his own feeling and the story of Kiki going out to the city alone and training is synchronized. I think that there is a part similar to Slow Start, Witch&amp;rsquo;s house. Both are brightly totally, but there are also a few paintings of the painful spots of reality. Because I changed the test, I feel in common where the strength of the heroine is born.  Tweet share - Next is the relay question corner. From last time Mr. Atsumi asked, If the director were a girl, who would you think is the closest among the four? (Laugh).  Hashimoto: Eiko, you&amp;rsquo;re right. I am a de Morono (lol). Ekiko also seems to be inviting a little for classmates, but it seems like S, but suddenly it looks like M in front of Enami. So when I draw Eikiko, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m understanding as if I&amp;rsquo;m doing it happily.  In the first place, the job of an animation director has a place like de M which is troubled by myself while annoying others. I think that I can turn the schedule well if Eikiko becomes the director (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share &amp;ndash;(Lol). Then ask questions to Mr. Inoue of the next series composition.  Hashimoto: If you were a man, whose boyfriend would you like to be? (Laugh). Not from the main 4 people, but from seven people including Enami, &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; Whatever you put in all the classmates (laugh). Mr. Inoue who knew the character as a series composition, it should be able to answer &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; and I tried to demonstrate S ___ 0.  - Please give a message to the reader at the end.  HASHIMOTO: Although Slow Start is a work with many sights, I&amp;rsquo;d like to have fans first enjoy themselves. From my fans, I was pleased that It was good that I became such animation. If I do not do that, animation will not get excited, and I&amp;rsquo;d like others to be proud of so Slow Start was funny from the front! (Laugh). It is my goal to make it work that you can say so.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Masaru Naganawa Masaru Naganawa Attractive appearance and personality gap in crown</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-masaru-naganawa-attractive-appearance-and-personality-gap-in-crown</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-masaru-naganawa-attractive-appearance-and-personality-gap-in-crown</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Interview with Masaru Naganawa Masaru Naganawa Attractive appearance and personality gap in crown From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo □ [Serial 2] Yuko Takura, Mr. Tomomi Ling Inside Carefully cherish the feeling that crown really wants to do - Please tell us from the impression when you first saw the crown (Sengoku) first.  Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, How small a child is, really a high school student (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child It became clear.  Tweet share - What do you think is the appeal of such a crown?  Naganawa: After all, is it a gap between appearance and personality? It is also the strength of the core that I said at the moment, although it is very small and it is cute, it is a big eater, it is surprisingly a poisonous tongue (laugh).  - Is there a place where Mr. Naganawa is sympathetic to the crown?  Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;hellip;, but even if I talk about being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.  Tweet share Tweet share - What do you care about playing the crown?  Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of doing things that the crown really wants to do. For example, when it comes to a story like I will give you better things next year about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks Hall cake is good It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).  Tweet share - Is there anything left in the impression on the interaction at the after-recording site? Either Cast or Staff.  Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, This performance is a bit more like this, you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) Welcome to Muku and feel like English? Like Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome to Mom, but it is interesting and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).  Full of feelings to say Sorry, gorilla!  - Have you also had a lecture on the crown?  Naganawa: I did not have much lectures, but I always thought I wanted to be blurred somewhere (laugh). While drinking, I think that it will be slightly different, I am going to put in an awkward ad lib, but mostly it says I do not need (laugh).  But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you Please add ad libs over there and said This foolish people. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought I&amp;rsquo;m happy!  Tweet share - Please let me know the scenes recommended by Ms. Nagana in other main contents.  Naganawa: In the sports test of episode 2, it is a place where a crown is caught and a cool shoulder is presented to a tired Hana name. But, after all, the two people slid down the banks, It was kind of coolly presented out! It was very fun together with the picture.  Tweet share There is a scene in which the crown is I am sorry, gorilla with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say I am sorry, gorilla as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.  - Also next week the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Sung by the main cast will be released on January 24th. Can you explain briefly what kind of song it is?  Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way No, no, no, but here four people have come to say no in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.  If you keep two pets and give it a name &amp;hellip;?  - Here is a question that changed the taste of the question a little, but how was it like when Ms. Naganawa was in high school?  Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard! It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic, so it seems like &amp;hellip; let&amp;rsquo;s do it (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.  Tweet share Tweet share - Er, is that in the school building?  Naganawa: It was a time of rebuilding, it was a prefabricated school building. But everyone was fine just to destroy the prefabricated floor (laugh).  - Next, I want to move to the section of relay question, but from last time Mr. Lingouchi said that he wanted to keep a cat before Mr. Naganawa said If you can keep a pet, I will keep what animal What is your name? Asked What is your name?  Nagano: I&amp;rsquo;m lost ~. A cat, a dog or a bird &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; For now, I will make cats and birds one by one. The type of cat is Munchkin, so its name is astringent &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The name of the pet is thinking when walking well, I do not have any (laugh). That&amp;rsquo;s why I thought about this, Seirin of a cat.  Tweet share Tweet share - Why is it such a Japanese name?  Nagan: What? You do not want twist? When asked, What do you mean cute cat?, What do you think? Wow? Cocoa? No, Mocha? No, I do not know The correct answer is Ki It was Ming!  Well, why did you want it? (Laugh). I want to laugh a lot (laugh).  - I see. (Laugh). So what is the other one?  Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval properly, I will become a scene like I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. Hayato (laugh). Because I want a reaction like Why ~? I know a friend you know.  - So, next question (hundred areas) I&amp;rsquo;d like to ask Aya Ito who is a role for a while.  Nagan: What is it &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip; Is it okay if I have nothing to do with the work? What experiment do you want to do? Everything is okay, even if you explore something, even if it explodes (laugh).  Tweet share -(Lol). Please give me a message to the readers at the end.  Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin against it and it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), as everyone&amp;rsquo;s ties deepen, everyone&amp;rsquo;s expression also I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.  In case Work information TV anime Slow Start Broadcast on January 6, 2018 (Tue) on air!  &lt;Broadcast information&gt; TOKYO MX, Taguchi TV, Gunma TV, BS 11: Every Saturday 24: 30 ~ Kansai Television: Every Thursday 26: 25 ~ TV Aichi: Every Tuesday 26: 05 - AT-X: Every Monday 20: 00 ~ ※ Every Wednesday 12: 00 ~ / every Friday 28: 00 ~ repeat broadcasting ※ Broadcast date and time may be changed due to circumstances of organization. Please note.  【Opening theme】 STARTails ☆ (Rena Kondo, Aya Ito, Tomomi Linouchi, Maria Naganawa) no! no! no!  Wednesday, January 24, 2018 released!  【STAFF】 Original: Atsumi Miko (Yoshifusa Manga Time Kirara series) Director: Hiroyuki Hashimoto Series composition: Mio Inoue Character design · total drawing director: Masato Yano Prop Design: Masako Ito Main animator: Yorito Yoshida Art director: Kisen Henibu Color design: Hoka Naka Nako CG Director: Shinji Nasu Director of Photography: Satoshi Kuroiwa Editing Acoustic director: Kawahito Meida Acoustic effect: Toshiya Wada Music: Yoshimasa Fujisawa Music production: Aniplex 制作：A-1 Pictures 【CAST】 Ichinose Hana&amp;rsquo;s name: Rina Kondo One hundred places before: Aya Ito Yuko Takakura: Tomonori Linouchi Sengoku crown: Maria Naganawa Shima Kyotuka: M · A · O Million Year Competition: Wadare Uchida Kiyoshi Enami: Manami Numakura TV anime Slow Start official website TV anime Slow Start Official Twitter (@ slosta_anime) &amp;copy; Atsumi Miko / Yoshifusashi / Slow Start Production Committee&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] 【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Yuko Takakura role interview with Mr. Tominari Ling Inside! What is the attention scene of the early story for Eiko</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-yuko-takakura-role-interview-with-mr.-tominari-ling-inside-what-is-the-attention-scene-of-the-early-story-for-eiko</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:27:17 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-series-tv-anime-slow-start-yuko-takakura-role-interview-with-mr.-tominari-ling-inside-what-is-the-attention-scene-of-the-early-story-for-eiko</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515724499&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1515724499&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;【Series】 TV anime Slow Start Yuko Takakura role interview with Mr. Tominari Ling Inside! What is the attention scene of the early story for Eiko From January 2018 TV animation Slow Start broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / Manga Time Kirara series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview targeting the main cast members and staff members is posted. It is Mr. Tomoko Ryouchi, Ms. Yuko Takura, Mr. Tominori Ling Inside who will appear in the second time! We have answered questions unique to Eiko, including the impression of the character we play.  Tweet share ■■■ Series Back Issues □ [Serial 1] Ikuase flower name role · Rena Kondo In case Eiko is the most ordinary girl in a sense - How was the first impression of Mr. Ekiko (Tokura) being played?  Yuko Takakura, Mr. Tominori Inouchi (hereinafter referred to as Morie): I thought that looks good, I thought it was a light girl with footwork. Indeed, not only the group of flower names but also the children of other groups are good friends, talking about (oh) that things like that (lol). But now I think that it is an interesting child who finds many new aspects as you see it. As the four people get along with each other, there are expressions and dialogue saying This is only for good friends.  Tweet share - What kind of place do you think is such charm of Noriko?  MIYAKI: I think that it is wonderful to have a very girl appearance. From the girls perspective, I think that it is Eiko as many points that I can empathize most. Behavior is not ordinary in many cases (lol), even when talking with others, I often look at the relationship between my friends and give priority to what people want to do rather than what I want to do, as well as family It is surprisingly normal and in some sense it is the most ordinary girl. Even from the viewpoint of men, I think that it is a child who is easy to understand as having a familiar feeling of becoming such a child!  Tweet share Tweet share - Do you feel that you resemble yourself?  Ryoke: In fact, Eikiko actually does not talk much when he&amp;rsquo;s four people. Temporarily speaking the most, about squeezing the mouth occasionally against it. I also like to see things about people, I often see that I&amp;rsquo;m thinking about this person like this rather than talking, I think that such a standing position is very close to me I will.  - On the contrary, where do you feel you can not imitate yourself?  Morie: You can not imitate the height of that communication skill (laugh). Among the works, there is a scene to talk to unknown people and listen to contacts, but I think that such place is not a normal child, it is a superhuman (laugh).  Tweet share - Is such a high school student&amp;rsquo;s departed aspect aware even though it can be played?  Inside: In other words, on the contrary, trying to be careful about not to become an adult too much. Even if it is said that it is a mature girl, I think that it is only a high school student to the last, just an adult compared with a classmate. When I am having fun, I smile like a high school student and I think that there is a certainty that I feel that I am a child after all in front of a citizen ???? or an adult.  &amp;ndash;I see. Have you done anything else to create a role?  Ryoke: Ei Niko has a sister, but since myself is a younger sister, I do not know much of her sister&amp;rsquo;s feelings. So, I remembered what girls around me, what kind of ideas and acts are done by my sister? Recently, I feel that Onee-chan was serious again (laugh).  Tweet share Tweet share - Please tell me if there are episodes, etc. that were impressive on the dubbing field.  Inside: After drinking is over, when you lend a ballpoint pen to Mr. Kondo, it is returned in a very natural way saying Eikiko chan! (Laugh). The person himself was surprised, Ah &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;. Sorry ~, I thought Wow! ~ At that time (laugh).  Conversation with Dr. Enoki Enoki is also an important scene for Eiko - Although the first episode was finally broadcasted the other day, is there a recommended scene at the beginning?  Lingyu: In the second episode, there is a scene where a conversation with Professor Enoki Enoki is drawn for the first time, but I was glad if you could keep it in mind as I played it with great care. In that scene I just do not have any other love conversations about ice, but because important scenes are also packed for Eiko, so it&amp;rsquo;s time for a future story to feel the delicate distance and relationship between the two I would like you to pay attention to what the future will change.  Tweet share - Also on January 24, the OP song ne! Ne! Ne! Sung by four people will be on sale. Can you explain briefly what kind of song it is?  Lingyu: I&amp;rsquo;m not too energetic, not too grown up, there are places that I feel a bit tricky, but there are energetic places like high school students, I think that it is a song that includes both aspects. I myself consciously thought of how I felt it was Sakaeiko, not to be too harsh, singing calmly.  - MVs sung by four people were also made.  Inside: MV was difficult to dance (laugh). But in the scene where four people gather and dance, there is the feeling of air of the four people who always have a close relationship with Slow Start, I felt it was really nice even if I danced. After that the set is fairly elaborate, especially since the projection mapping of the background is really amazing, I am surprised to see it, I think I can get it!  - Then it will be a little private question, but what kind of high school days did you live by Mr. Lingouchi?  Inside: In the afternoon I was doing a popular app while eating rice with a good boy. So, when I watch the scenes that eat lunch for four people at Slow Start, I think that I was like this every day, I miss it.  Also did the sports test. I do not have physical strength, but I liked the movement and I was good at the ball game, so I became understand ~! To serifs such as Mr. Ekiko&amp;rsquo;s Distance is great but control is good (Laugh).  - In this interview series we have established a relay question section. Last time, Mr. Kondo (Rena) who is the name of a flower has come up with a question saying What fashion do you like about fashionable Noriko who is?  Inside: Fashion? I like the dress very much. I like the shape as I can pat on the top and bottom. My jeans have not got a single suit, the skirt calms down.  Tweet share Tweet share - In addition, it is pin although speaking of Ekiko &amp;hellip; &amp;hellip;.  Inside: Ah, since I started Slow Start, I have more hairpins than Nico. Until then I did not have almost attached it, but recently even myself, I came to search for something cute hairpin. Even Mr. Atsumi of the original, I got a hairpin that seems to be very proud of her birthday gift, I thought a teacher truly ~, so I would like to add it even at the release event.  - Then, do you have any questions you would like to ask Mr. Naganawa (Maria) who will appear next?  Ridai: That&amp;rsquo;s right &amp;hellip; Well then, since Mr. Naganawa said that he would like to have a cat if she can keep it, What kind of animals do you keep if you can keep a pet, and how do you name it? Oh, the crown has two cats, nagomi and cosmetic, so two animals!  Tweet share - Please give a message to the audience at the end.  Lingyu: Four people have just met yet, but as the talk progresses, the distance feeling of everyone gets closer and the response also changes, so I&amp;rsquo;m happy if everyone talks about such a change in relationship. Since I think that I can not say that my true feelings are not good friends, I hope that you can accumulate among all of us that you are such a child that is actually such a child  , I think that you can see more and more fun.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[English] Slow Start Sengoku Crown Interview with Masaru Naganawa! The appearance and character gap between the crown is attractive</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-slow-start-sengoku-crown-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-the-appearance-and-character-gap-between-the-crown-is-attractive</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:26:10 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/english-slow-start-sengoku-crown-interview-with-masaru-naganawa-the-appearance-and-character-gap-between-the-crown-is-attractive</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Translate : &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&#34;&gt;https://www.animatetimes.com/news/details.php?id=1516333521&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I did not have much lectures, but I always thought I wanted to be blurred somewhere (laugh). While drinking, I think that it will be slightly different, I am going to put in an awkward ad lib, but mostly it says &amp;lsquo;I do not need&amp;rsquo; (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: In the sports test of episode 2, it is a place where a crown is &amp;lsquo;caught&amp;rsquo; and a cool shoulder is presented to a tired Hana name. But, after all, the two people slid down the banks, &amp;lsquo;It was kind of coolly presented out!&amp;rsquo; It was very fun together with the picture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Next I would like to move to the relay question section, but from last time Mr. Lingouchi said that he wanted to keep a cat before Ms. Naganawa said &amp;lsquo;If you can keep a pet, I will keep what animal What is your name? &amp;lsquo;Asked&amp;rsquo; What is your name? &amp;lsquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagano: I&amp;rsquo;m lost ~. A cat, a dog or a bird &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; For now, I will make cats and birds one by one. The type of cat is Munchkin, so its name is astringent &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; The name of the pet is thinking when walking well, I have not kept it (laugh). That&amp;rsquo;s why I thought about this, &amp;lsquo;Seirin&amp;rsquo; of a cat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: What? You do not want twist? When asked, &amp;lsquo;What do you mean cute cat?&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;What do you think?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Wow? Cocoa?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;Mocha?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;No,&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I do not know&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;The correct answer is Ki It was Ming! &amp;ldquo; Well, why did you want it? &amp;lsquo;(Laugh). I want to laugh a lot (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From January 2018 TV animation &amp;lsquo;Slow Start&amp;rsquo; broadcasting at TOKYO MX and others, (Original: Atsumi Masako / &amp;lsquo;Manga Time Kirara&amp;rsquo; series serial). In the Animate Times, in conjunction with the official website, a long version of a series project &amp;lsquo;animate Times Presents Slow Start Relay Interview&amp;rsquo; targeting everyone in the main cast and the staff is posted. It is Mr. Masaru Naganawa who is Mr. Sengoku, who will appear in the third one! We have answered questions unique to the crown, including the impression of the character we perform.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Masaru Sengoku, Mari Naganawa (hereinafter, Naganawa): When I read the original work at the beginning, I thought, &amp;lsquo;How small a child is, really a high school student&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Even when I introduce myself in class, I&amp;rsquo;m pulling in shy and knowing that my hair is fluffy and small animal series. But as I read it, I do not have a few words, but I told you something that everybody did not feel comfortable saying, or something like that, &amp;lsquo;I think, unexpectedly the core is a strong child&amp;rsquo; It became clear.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: The crown has few speech lines and scripts are often written as &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;, but even if I talk about it being one-on-one, as soon as three or more people talk, they will not talk soon, so high school When I was having lunch with a group in the group, I was trying to eat it ~ (laugh), that is similar. Just listening to everyone &amp;rsquo;s talking is fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: I think crowns are a very selfish child. It&amp;rsquo;s really straightforward for what I want and what I want to do, so when I am playing it, I&amp;rsquo;m cherishing the feeling of &amp;lsquo;doing things that the crown really wants to do&amp;rsquo;. For example, even when it comes to a story like &amp;lsquo;I will deliver better things next year&amp;rsquo; about birthday gifts for Hana Hana in the first episode, the crown that I kept till then suddenly thinks &amp;lsquo;Hall cake is good&amp;rsquo; It is like saying his own greed like something like that (laugh). It&amp;rsquo;s really fun when playing the crown at my own pace (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: When Mr. Acoustic Director says, &amp;lsquo;This performance is a bit more like this,&amp;rsquo; you actually do a sample and show us. For example, I&amp;rsquo;m lectured to Reinan (Kondo) as &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Muku and feel like English?&amp;rsquo; Like &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Wonderful, Welcome ~&amp;rsquo; but it is fun and everyone is always I am laughing (laugh).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, there was a scene in which a crown wears a tiara in a dress shape and is praised by a person because of the imaginary delusion when talking about the origin of the name in the first episode. I told you &amp;lsquo;Please add ad libs&amp;rsquo; over there and said &amp;lsquo;This foolish people&amp;rsquo;. Then I laughed very much beyond the booth, I became OK and I thought &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;m happy!&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is a scene in which the crown is &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; with a certain number of stories in the last round. From the time I read the scenario, this line was personally pointed and filled with the desire to say &amp;lsquo;I am sorry, gorilla&amp;rsquo; as soon as it is after dubbing (laugh). So please look forward to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nagan: It&amp;rsquo;s a song that you can listen to and feel gentle. There are places on the way &amp;lsquo;No, no, no,&amp;rsquo; but here four people have come to say &amp;lsquo;no&amp;rsquo; in turn, so that the friends feel friendly from each other like this I thought. Also, on MV &amp;rsquo;s recording day, four people are playing on mobile and taking pictures, something is in youth (laugh). From that day, the relationship between the four people has deepened.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: My high school was a girls&amp;rsquo; school, but everyone was doing very well. Even in the morning, &amp;lsquo;Hello, good morning ~! Today is going to work hard!&amp;rsquo; It hugs me (laugh). It is normal driving, I was not so energetic so it seems like &amp;lsquo;&amp;hellip; Good luck&amp;rsquo; (laugh). The most surprising thing was that as the people ran through the corridor, the floor came out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganuma: I will make the bird frame cockatoo. Is not she really cute? My parents also have botanical birds and I like birds, but I imitate cockatrooms and will sing. But if I can not remember it, after singing &amp;lsquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve lost my musical interval&amp;rsquo; properly, I will become a scene like &amp;lsquo;I made a mistake now &amp;hellip;&amp;rsquo;. The touching feeling is very cute, similar to human beings. As for the name, it is nice to have a Japanese style, but I&amp;rsquo;d like a name like this. &amp;lsquo;Hayato&amp;rsquo; (laugh). Because I want a reaction like &amp;lsquo;Why ~?&amp;rsquo; &amp;lsquo;I know something in a acquaintance&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Naganawa: I think some people viewing up until the second episode feel uneasy how Hana Names will get along with everyone from now on, but after the third episode, Hana also has a more heart Tama is going to be open, Tama is becoming a child full of more gags, Ekiko &amp;rsquo;s gentle tsukkin&amp;rsquo; s response to it, it is a strict correspondence of the crown (laugh), everyone &amp;rsquo;s expression also goes along with deepening our mutual ties I think that I would like to see it while having fun because I will increase more and more. Thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】ブラッククローバー 19</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_black_clover_episode_19_discussion</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 12:02:24 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_black_clover_episode_19_discussion</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x8row/spoilers_black_clover_episode_19_discussion/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x8row/spoilers_black_clover_episode_19_discussion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃スポイラー内&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これがソースマテリアルコーナーです！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントに返信して、今後のスポイラーについて議論したり、今週のエピソードを元のエピソードと比較したり、原材料について話したりするだけです。元のソースを見たことがない場合は、ここにスポイラーがあることに注意してください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントの外にあるソースの議論は削除され、このコメントに向けられます。反復犯罪は禁止につながる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃警告する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;#Noelle &amp;hellip;カバーアップ&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[]（＃Kobeniblush）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ロッキーは彼のwaifuを殺しましたか？名前：うん。名前：だから彼らは基本的に彼は彼の友人を殺すように強制&amp;hellip;ダイヤモンド王国を愛する！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Oooooo彼らはロッキーを融合させ、彼の本がなぜそんなに見えるのかというと、それはちょっと冷たい。彼らが永遠に一緒にできることを意味します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ゆのは加速していますか？この減速する灰色の世界は私にアクセラワールドを思い出させる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ああ、彼の加速の世界の中でloliの妖精を見てください。ちょうどカジュアルで怠惰な、ロリの妖精のように。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そして彼女はちょうど1匹の岩を打った。 OP Blizz、Nerf plz。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;待って、アスタの剣は何をしていますか？彼の本に新しい剣が追加されたと思いますか？だから私は彼の今のことを意味すると思います。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;もちろん、アスタはロッキーも救いたいと思っています。 Astaはこの世界にはあまりにもいい。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;みんな一緒に働いて、ここから出てきてね。きちんとした私はこのように一緒に働くことができる差別的能力を​​持つ人々を見るのが大好きです。その素晴らしい組み合わせ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;LOLスモーキーもそれを作り出し、たくさんの盗品を盗んだ。 xDヘイズはかなり素晴らしい。ああ、彼はロッキーを救った。この古い男は陽気です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ロッキーの火のように見えるウェイフは、彼が逃げ出して自由になることを望んでいた。セックスはかなり素晴らしい。彼女は死んでしまったが、彼女はロッキーの心の中に住んでいる。待って&amp;hellip;彼らは彼女を彼に入れたのですか？彼はフランケンシュタインの魔術師のようになっている&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そしてAstaはすべて上質です。多かれ少なかれ&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;待っていたメガネくんは、アスタとゆーのために謙虚になっていますか？彼は途中で頭に打たれましたか？あなたはメガネくんを瀕死にしていますか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そして、ノエレは、彼女のおっぱいが過去のエピソードをぶら下げていることを実感しています&amp;hellip;笑&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;まあ私はその弧を終了すると思います。 YunoとAstaの両方が新しい力を得て、もう少し成長しました。悪くない。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;だからここからどこへ行くのだろう。私はベースと次のミッションとに戻ると思います。そのショーは51のepsとなり、それは19でしかないと思うのは少し奇妙です。まだ32 eps！&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】おそ松さん 第2期 19</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_osomatsusan_2_episode_19_discussion</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_osomatsusan_2_episode_19_discussion</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x2vug/spoilers_osomatsusan_2_episode_19_discussion/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x2vug/spoilers_osomatsusan_2_episode_19_discussion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃スポイラー内&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これがソースマテリアルコーナーです！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントに返信して、今後のスポイラーについて議論したり、今週のエピソードを元のエピソードと比較したり、原材料について話したりするだけです。元のソースを見たことがない場合は、ここにスポイラーがあることに注意してください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントの外にあるソースの議論は削除され、このコメントに向けられます。反復犯罪は禁止につながる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃警告する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は兄弟が狂気にあたってお互いにバレンタインチョコレートを与えるようになっても、トーティーはまだ笑ってしまった&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは、おそらく、私が第2校のエピソードで笑ったことのほとんどです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;世界がトランプと彼の大統領をどのように見ているかについての最初の討論は論評であったか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;LOLは誰もTottyを愛していない&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼らはFappymatsuに余分な時間をもう一度与えた&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はトトコと少年たちがチョコレート・スキットでシーズン1と同じようにやってくれてうれしいです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;誰もトッティ・チョコレートをくれません&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】からかい上手の高木さん 6</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_karakai_jouzu_no_takagisan_episode_6</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_karakai_jouzu_no_takagisan_episode_6</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x1ylh/spoilers_karakai_jouzu_no_takagisan_episode_6/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x1ylh/spoilers_karakai_jouzu_no_takagisan_episode_6/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃スポイラー内&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これがソースマテリアルコーナーです！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントに返信して、今後のスポイラーについて議論したり、今週のエピソードを元のエピソードと比較したり、原材料について話したりするだけです。元のソースを見たことがない場合は、ここにスポイラーがあることに注意してください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントの外にあるソースの議論は削除され、このコメントに向けられます。反復犯罪は禁止につながる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃警告する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西田はこのエピソードであまりにも多くのジャンプの怖さに犠牲者だった。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は、高木さんが性格を崩して、西方を気にしていることを真に示している珍しい瞬間が本当に好きです&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/PhpfCcu.png&#34; alt=&#34;The cutest jump scare&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/qb8ueIn.png&#34; alt=&#34;I can&#39;t believe the spawn of the devil can be this cute&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;高木が西方と恋に落ちたのかな？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西方は夏の終わりまでにそれらのすべてのプッシュアップで裂かれます&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/wIoyZYF.png&#34; alt=&#34;aww, Takagi was actually really sad when Nishikata fell down.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;第6週レポート：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はまだ私の顔にばかな笑みを浮かべている。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このショーはとても健康的です&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/n71smKD.png&#34; alt=&#34;Hmmmmmm?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;この番組が始まったときに戻って、私は24分のエピソード構造がこのようなもののために働くだろうとは思っていませんでした。私たちは中途半端なので、私はエピソードを長くしたい。彼らのダイナミックさはとても甘いです。高橋理恵がこの甘い声を奏でるのを知らなかった。 &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これが続くと、西田はGeneral Armstrongに変わります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;大丈夫??&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私の心&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![&lt;a href=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/D9KtU8o.jpg)&#34;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/D9KtU8o.jpg)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/Fh0THGD.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Mina&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/uiChgNT.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;I-indirect k-kissu!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://i.imgur.com/M1KPQfr.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Such a cutie as always!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼女が何のために得たものを見るのを待つことはできません&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;割引&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;アニメは愛について私に非現実的な期待を与えた&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はこれらの2人が結婚している子供たちがいる続編シリーズが欲しい。そこでは高木が西田とその息子の両方を弄ぶエピソードを過ごす。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そして、それは、私の毎週の可愛らしさの用量&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは週に始まる最高のショーです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;高木が西方を愛しているのと同じくらい、このショーが大好きです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ガールズ、空腹の勇気の試練で、西方が夏の服装で可愛いタカギを見たときに、インストルメンタルバージョンのOP「岩合kedo ne」がプレイされます。なぜこれは重要なのでしょうか？岩内憲王の全体像は「私はあなたが好きだが、私はそれを認めない」それは沈んでみましょう。OPは高木の視点から来たはずですが、ここでは西田の視点からの曲のバージョンです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;tl; drでも音楽は価値があるdiabeetusです&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;神様このショーはとてもかわいい&amp;gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このショーは実際にはモートバージョンのナガトロをいじめないでください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私の心はそれぞれのエピソードでただ溶けているだけです。高木がニシカタを弄ぶシーンは、あまりにも恵まれています。高橋理恵は神です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;高木さんは休日に彼女を見るために西田を騙します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はまた、ハンカチのハンドオーバーが象徴的であることを発見しました。ちょうど彼女が自分自身を彼に渡していることを確認したかのように&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そのタンデムライディングは私にFranXXのバイブを与えていた。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼らはトンネルにいたときどこに隠れたのだろうか？それはまっすぐなトンネルなので、彼女は出口までずっと戻っていれば隠れていたかもしれませんが、彼女はそれを作れませんでした。そして、西田は彼女を見たでしょう。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西川はなぜ寝返りを心配しているのですか？彼は夏休みにいるので、彼が望むだけ寝ることができます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;高木が西方に水を投げる部分は終わりです。彼らも同じ服を着ています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私たちは、タンデムに乗る最後の男のことを少し嫉妬していますか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは幸いにも甘くなり始めています。私はそれをバランスを取るためにいくつかの柑橘類に混ぜるべきだと思います。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;編集：実際には、Mitsoboshiの色が私に何かを教えていれば、ショーは特定の尊厳を欠いているということを知っています。 ^^^^^ a ^^^^^ moestache&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/qqS2zQ5.png&#34; alt=&#34;Shirou level&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/B4uYB1V.png&#34; alt=&#34;Worried Takagi&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このショーは、文字通り最高の私を迎えてくれます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/Ca58Myi.png&#34; alt=&#34;Cutest Jumpscare ever&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;この時点で誰も高木を打つことはできません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ダン、私はそのEDが大好きです。私はそれが最後のエピソードに気付かなかったとは信じられません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はちょうどEDの各シーンが曲のビートに変化していることに気づいた。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼女はちょうど日付！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;すべての深刻さで私は彼が少なくとも一度リードを取っているように思っています。そのトンネルは、彼女の手をつかんで彼女と一緒に走るのに最適な時間でした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は、高木が夏休みに西方なしでどう対処するのだろうと思っていた。しかし、彼女は彼女が彼女と時間を過ごす理由を作ることに成功しました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西方が友人と一緒に浜辺に行っていたら、高木はどうしたらいいだろうか。私は彼女がちょうど起こっただろうと想像して、私は確かに彼が彼女に偶然起こったすべての時間は偶然だったとは思わない。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;タンデムバイク（うまくいけば）を見るためにもう一週間待たなければならないようです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/HZWHL65.png&#34; alt=&#34;again biking alone&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;FNAF 7アニメ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;シーズンのOTP。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ああ、私の神様、このアニメはすべてのエピソードでよりかわいくてかわいくなります！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;「」（＃うわあ）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;何とか西川を見ていると、毎週絶対に支配してしまうのです。今シーズン私の好きなショーになるのを待って、私は大声で笑って、怒っている画面で叫ぶ。ちょうど地獄として愛らしい。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西川と高木は^^^^足を一緒に浴びます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は彼らが既に退屈な女の子のトリオセグメントでやめたいと思っています。彼らはショーに何も加えず、全体の質を低下させるだけです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;あなたは彼女のスカートを裏返すことによって日付にすることができます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;西田はあらゆる可能な場面で自分自身を引き出しています。彼が残りのエピソードで一度高木を得るなら、私は驚くだろう&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このショーは毎週私の最も待望され続けています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;一番かわいい冬のショーの一つ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;最後のスキットは非常にさわやかだった、私は彼女の世話をする側の理由から、おしゃべりが古くなってきたからです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;3人の女の子と一緒のビットは、私にAzumanga Daiohのような古典的なSOLのことを思い出させる。それは素晴らしい。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;また、高木は特にこのエピソードを愛していました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;最初のスキットは品質部門で少し下がった。アニメーションは非常に堅いように見え、動きはあまりありませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;一方、他のすべてのスキットは、非常に素晴らしいアニメーションを持っていて、多くの流体の動き&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は本当に授業の担当者が氷を食べて音楽を止めて宿題を話し始める部分が大好きだったが、眉毛やぼんやりとしたパンチが目を覚ました&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;全体的にかわいいエピソード&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このショーは、ニシカタのために悪い気持ちを止めてからもう少し耐えられるようになってきました。彼はとてもばかげているので、彼は自分が得たものに値する。そして、はい、私は彼が12歳のようなことを知っています。年を取った子供たちと仕事をしたことで、彼らは完全に学習と成長ができると言うことができます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;今日のエピソードは素晴らしかった！とてもかわいいと私はエピソードを通して笑顔を持っていた。このシーズンの残りの部分はこのままにしてください&amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ちょうどufoTableがこのショーのクレジットにあることを実感しました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは、過大予算のアクションシーンの代わりに、 &amp;ldquo;awwwwww&amp;rdquo;のパートタイムで働いているシーズンでなければなりません&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;トンネル内の悪意ある幽霊と神秘的な消滅についてのそれらの物語すべて、そして高木はまだその中で最も恐ろしい事であることを管理します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは実際に私が見た最初のショーであり、それは私にすべてのマンガを読ませたいと思っていて、アニメ化されたかわいいインタラクションがたくさん見られないのは悲しいことです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;つまり、アニメーション化されていなければ、ショーが終了するととても失望するだろうという1つの章があります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は私の体の糖尿病を感じることができます&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;文字通りこれとスピンオフのマンガを今すぐダウンロード&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はちょうど &amp;ldquo;彼女を抱きしめろ！&amp;rdquo;と思って、エピソード全体を過ごす。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/Jsmyy6i.png&#34; alt=&#34;Isn&#39;t that just… wine?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私が外に出ていると思うと、彼らは私を引き戻す。錦田はついにそれを手に入れ始めた。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;UNは落ちた。 :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;トンネルで怖がっている西田を責めることはできない。それは恐ろしいジャンプカットでした！ （いいえ、本当は）。私が行ってきたいくつかの日付よりもまだ良い。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼の友達は醜いです&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.redd.it/afh5fp5birf01.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;this has nothing to doe with the episode, I just needed to post it somewhere&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】りゅうおうのおしごと！ 6</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_ryuuou_no_oshigoto_episode_6_discussion</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_ryuuou_no_oshigoto_episode_6_discussion</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x19p3/spoilers_ryuuou_no_oshigoto_episode_6_discussion/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x19p3/spoilers_ryuuou_no_oshigoto_episode_6_discussion/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃スポイラー内&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これがソースマテリアルコーナーです！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントに返信して、今後のスポイラーについて議論したり、今週のエピソードを元のエピソードと比較したり、原材料について話したりするだけです。元のソースを見たことがない場合は、ここにスポイラーがあることに注意してください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントの外にあるソースの議論は削除され、このコメントに向けられます。反復犯罪は禁止につながる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃警告する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;将棋満載のエピソード。最終的に彼の将棋エピソードを持っている龍&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;将棋で何が起こっているのか分からず、4年間チェスをした人として、これらの試合はかなり誇大宣伝です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;うまくいけば、私たちはもう少しキャラクターの進行を得ると、彼は私が竜王のタイトルのためにあるべきだと思う彼の次の試合に対抗する方法を見つけ出す&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;最初のエピソード&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私：これはロリショーではない、それはただのキャラクターで、子供の天才は聞いたことがない。これはちょうどアニメユーモアです。加えて、日本将棋協会の支持を得ています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt; 2番目のAIが導入されました&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はAIを価値ある相手にすることは理にかなっており、彼女の技能（技術的な開口力、理論的知識）はAIの難しさを軽視することなく、難易度を上げるのにぴったりです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;研究グループが導入されました&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これはすべて現実主義のためのものですが、もちろん、子供はすぐに専門家にジャンプしないで、年齢の違う人と遊んで、友達にすることは良いことです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は&amp;hellip;ええと&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;ショルダーメッセージ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;いくつかのtsundere shenanigansのための良い瞬間 -&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[]（＃blankblink）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[]（#cokemasterrace）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;それはすぐにエスカレートした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;彼の上に足を踏み入れる彼の全体のロリヘムを得て、彼はそれを大いに楽しんだ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;MRW：[]（＃エトタマドンノ）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;将棋選手（いいえ、プロではない）として、このエピソードは素晴らしく、みんなのために何かを持っていた。しかし、Crunchyrollのサブシステムは、「操作」や「ポジショニング」が良い選択であった「sabaki」の翻訳として「取引」を使用していました。文字通り翻訳するのは簡単なことではありません。私は実際に、このエピソードでは、Sangatsu no Lionのほとんどの場合よりも戦略のコンバージョンが少し好きです&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![&lt;a href=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/UvkNlTe.png)&#34;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/UvkNlTe.png)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;どこでアイ・アルターですか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ちょうどいくつかの迅速な燃焼の質問。クイズゥルウ、ヤイチはどれくらい強いの？彼が竜王であるにもかかわらず、彼は研究者とマエストロの両方に迷ったようですね？彼は他の2人と比べて何人のダンスを持っていますか？彼は銀杏さんより強いですか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;その間に、関東と関西の両方の地域でいつも異なる場所にいるようで、旅行には時間がかかるようです。なぜ、東京などのある場所にこだわってそこで遊ぶのではないのですか？ありがとうございました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;チャーちゃんはまだ最高の女の子&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はこれまでのこのシリーズが好きですが、私はMCが自分よりも弱くなっていると感じています.LNからアニメへの移行で失われたものかどうか疑問に思っています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼は涼ですが、彼は世界でも最高の存在ですが、彼から見たことは、彼が苦労していることです（アイアンのような完全なアマチュアに対してさえ）。これまでのところ、チュニ男に対する彼の唯一の勝利ではない？そして彼はとにかくそれを噛んだ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;我々は彼が超強力だと言われていますが、それは表示されていないようです。そして、彼は今、彼のプレイスタイルを完全に変えるために、より強くなるように訓練している&amp;hellip;それは彼が龍になる前にやっただろうか？私は知らないよ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は引き裂かれていますが、キャラクターの物語と進歩は少し弱いですが素晴らしいです。あなたに背中のマッサージを与えていると言われているのは、私が見守っている理由だけかもしれない&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼の弟が彼にマッサージをしてもらうようにしていた誰かが、私はそれが天国であることを確かめることができます。今私の兄弟だけが3人のかわいいlolisだったら、それは完璧だったでしょう。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はどこから来たのか、このシーンは違法だと確信しています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は将棋ではなく萌えの女の子のためにこのショーを見る&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;八一一郎を初めて迎えた相手の記録は面白かった、同じ人に数回失っても何度か自分の立場が変わったのだろうか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これはこのシリーズの最初のエピソードで、私には不満が残っています&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;その他の世界：「あなたのショーでは、小学生のキャラクターを描写してはいけません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;![Japan: &lt;a href=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/0qThKCm.png)&#34;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/0qThKCm.png)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;あなたのお姉さんがあなたの顔を踏み出すためにあなたのロリ・ヘレムだけに歩み寄って、いつもあなたを賞賛し、将棋を介してオンになっている変わった男に初めてあなたのことを教えてください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;うーん、このシリーズは本当に奇妙で、いくつかの点で真剣にしようとすると、ランダムなloliの嫌悪者は次の&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;チャイ、アヤノ、ミオの発展と探求を見てみたいと思います。ヤイチは、現在の相手を打ち負かす戦略を考え出しています。私は、彼女の裏話と性格のほとんどが探究されていない時、ミオと共感するのに苦労しました。ミオ、シャル、アヤノは、三人の友人がどれほど行動するかを考慮して、将棋のメンタリングを改善するための主弟子のために、日比谷藍に貢献する役割を果たしていると推測しています。しかし、それは残念です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;後半は、愛、銀杏、八一、慶応との葛藤をどのように進歩的で自然な形で見せてくれるのだろうか。エピソード6では、すべての問題が適切に解決されていないと、話が崩れることがあります。私は希望がある。これはおそらくアニメの最初のエピソードで、ストーリーがどのように続くか心配しているようです。少なくとも、ロリ・セニアニガンと将棋の試合は非常に面白いですが、どのようにそれはすべて恩返しになりますか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは将棋アニメと思われていた。 loliはアニメを恋しくない。まだかわいくて楽しい時計&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;左の女の子はakameからkillを私に思い出させる&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;だから&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;学校でこのエピソードを見るのが安全かどうか誰にでも教えてもらえますか&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;興味深いエピソード。彼がタイトルに達したにもかかわらず、私たちのprotagはまだ仕事を入れたいと思っています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;また、すごい銀杏、ロマンチックな光の中でこの男があなたを見ないのは不思議ですか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;将棋の試合中に話をするのはどうですか？許可されていますか？そうじゃない？許可されていますが、タブー/無礼と見なされますか？そのNatagiriの男が絶えずたわごとを話して、意図的に相手を離しているので、かなりおっしゃって、スポーツマンではないようです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;待って、どのようにNatagiriは反撃したのですか？その全体が「私はそれを受け取ります」ということですか？このアニメはとても楽しいですが、私は将棋について何も知らない人として、私は迷子になる傾向があります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ゲイスタート！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Keikaはおそらくokプレイヤーだが、シーンに遅れて参加することによって妨げられたことが明らかになった。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ある意味では、なぜ彼女が彼女のキャリアに遅れているように見えますが、まだ潜在的な可能性を秘めています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はこれがまさにこの時点でロリコン餌であることを意味する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;6つのエピソードの後、この番組はたわごとのスクリプトです、それはロリファンサービスとマゾヒスト男性ファンサービスのための理由だけです。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】フルメタル・パニック！ 9</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilersrewatch_full_metal_panic_episode_9</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilersrewatch_full_metal_panic_episode_9</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3iul/spoilersrewatch_full_metal_panic_episode_9/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3iul/spoilersrewatch_full_metal_panic_episode_9/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;一方、SousukeとKalininとの関係は、Solid SnakeとBig Bossの幸せな代替履歴バージョンであることがわかります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/AvjSq20.png&#34; alt=&#34;Chidori stopping by Sousuke&#39;s&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/cLIg4oV.png&#34; alt=&#34;Chidori&#39;s hair mass has begun to surpass the rest of her body.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/3hHsKgW.png&#34; alt=&#34;DON&#39;T PANIC&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;あなたたちは速く動いている&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はこれらの年と人の後にこのショーをもう一度見ています、私はあなたに教えてください、古い学校のアニメは今日とはとても異なっています。その壮大な、私たちがどれだけ遠くに来たのか。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;だから今私たちは心理的な恐怖をやっている？私たちが触れることができないジャンルはありませんか？どんなところでも、私は乗り込んでいます。子供がゆっくりとしたネクタイに心を奪われるのを見ていると、これまでのショーではおそらく最高の緊張の一部だったでしょう。そして、片方向のガラスを通してテッサをまっすぐに見てください。ああ、イエス。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そしてちょっとカリーニン、誰かがガンポルトにいる時、多分 &amp;ldquo;私はあなたの敵だ&amp;rdquo;というのは、最善のオープナーではない。ちょっとした考え。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;SousukeがLNでChidoriに与えた贈り物を読んでいた今私はショーにとどまっていたことを願います。それは面白いです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/3hHsKgW.png&#34; alt=&#34;It was at that moment that Sousuke knew - he fucked up.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このエピソードでは、深刻さとユーモアがうまく調和していて、defはかなり大きなものを設定しているようです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;最初に、このテロ組織にこの子供がいるか、あるいは彼がそれらによって使用されていたかもしれないが、彼はラムダ・ドライバーを使用する潜在的候補者のいずれかと思われる。今、この子供がとても狂っているので、私はミスリルが彼をどのように利用したいと思っているのか分かりませんが、私は不思議な思いです。テッサリストがこの子供のために病院を破壊するのに必死で、テッサをその潜水艦から引き離すのに十分な重要性を持っているならば、彼は今後の出来事に対処するためのデフになるだろう。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;いつものように、私たちはSosukeからいくつかの高級感を得ており、彼、Tessa、Kanameとの最終シーンは金色でした！テッサは私の上で成長していますが、実際にはあまり出すぎていませんが、なぜ彼女が彼女のポジションにいるのかを知りたいのは非常に興味があります。私は彼女が漱石と同じ年齢ですが、彼女の役割に有能である。今、私はそのポジションにいる理由を見てもらっていませんので、私たちはもっと早く見つけたいと思っています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;KanameのSosukeへの行動と謝罪、そして最後の発汗は、少なくとも私の未知の意見では、何らかのキャラクターの進行を示していた。 ：PそれはKanameの爆発の一部が少し不当にされているように感じる、ここで私たちは彼女がそれをある程度認識することを開始を参照してください。この実現の瞬間がなければ、Sosukeに向けられた彼女のテイラーのいくつかは少し古くなってきたかもしれませんが、これは心配を緩和するのに役立ちました。また、彼女には食べ物もあまりにも美味しかったですが、気分は悪いタイミングでした!!ここでは、ソンスケが何らかの関係にあると思っている場合、ソナスケがカナメに対する社会的義務の一部を把握し始めていると感じました。そして、貧しい人は悪い状況で立ち往生できませんでした！そして、彼の指揮官がちょうど彼と同じ年齢のかわいい女の子になることはあまりにも偶然のことです！これは本当にこれを平滑にするための偶然の言い訳以上のものです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;さて、明らかに私は正しく覚えていませんでした（私は良い実績があるわけではありません）。そしてこのエピソードは私のお気に入りの一つではありません。私は最後にそれをリワッチしてから50年以上経ちました&amp;hellip;&amp;gt;&amp;gt;私はFumoffuのエピソードをLOLの代わりに考えていました。うん&amp;hellip;これは私がこれを見直している間違いなく良いことです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;テッサとのあらゆるエピソードは良いエピソードですが。 ：Pパラシュートのドロップインも楽しいものでした。そして最後のすすけの顔は陽気だった！それは女性を怒らせた男の顔です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;今、フランチャイズ全体の中で私の最も好きな弧を入力&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ありがたいことに、それは長いものではなく、我々は取引を甘くするためにテッサの多くを得る。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私のお気に入りのアーチではありませんが、TessaとKanameがこのエピソードでどのように会うのが大好きです。本当に今後の関係を固めます。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】マクロスＦ（ロンティア） 12</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/macross_rewatch_macross_frontier_episode_12</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/macross_rewatch_macross_frontier_episode_12</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3af9/macross_rewatch_macross_frontier_episode_12/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3af9/macross_rewatch_macross_frontier_episode_12/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[それで、これに来ました。]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://streamable.com/9jm1b）&#34;&gt;https://streamable.com/9jm1b）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;今回はプロットが大規模なスキームの一部に過ぎませんが、私たちは前回のエピソードでそれを見ていますが、それはまだよく見ていません。私たちは、Graceがインプラントを通して電話をかけたり受けたりするのを見ました。そして、演説の途中でTemjin（a.k.a.Nu！Quamzin）に電話する人は誰ですか？プロッタがマイケルがランカと出会うことを予想していたようには見えないが、ランカが歌い始めるとき、グレースはいつものクールデタッチメントよりも高い関心を示している。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このシリーズが最初に言及したFold Faultsの問題は、プロットを適度に重要なものに変えています。 LAIは、ユニークなFold Boosterでテストしているソリューションを見つけました。これは誰のベーコンの節約にも便利です。そして、ちょっと、Lucaがこれまでのところよりも少しだけ関連性の高いチャンスです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ランカはアルトのために歌ったり、おそらくゼントラディに戦いを止めさせることから、かなり大きな信頼を得ることができます。 Sherylが現時点で手数料を払っていないので、輝く彼女の時間のように見えます。彼女とアルトは最終的に別の巨大なオリジナルのシリーズリファレンスにクラッシュする必要があります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[「青函彦」武道館ライブ！]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I10ZBspLbMA）&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I10ZBspLbMA）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[Platina Jazzバージョン]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=351cD3wZuUc）&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=351cD3wZuUc）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[「Neko Nikki」タイムリーサブタイトルのフルバージョン]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FX-HyEnNjk8）&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FX-HyEnNjk8）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;「「おおっえええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええええ -  Deculture Editionのサイズ]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://streamable.com/pqlnz）&#34;&gt;https://streamable.com/pqlnz）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/DwL46ew.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&amp;quot;Don&#39;t be a racist old guy.&amp;quot;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/QBVwExQ.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&amp;quot;Don&#39;t be an idiot, Alto!&amp;quot;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/wo47grt.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&amp;quot;No weird hitchhikers!&amp;quot;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;第33海軍艦隊は本質的に反乱の途中にあります。シェリルからのコンサートを受けなければ、オーダーに従わずに反撃することを拒否しているゼントラディの大グループがあります。それは奇妙な要求ですが、Zentradiは常にアイドルの音楽を愛しています。さらに、基本的に言い訳にすぎません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;シェリルは崩壊する。致命的なアニメの流行が彼女に追いついた。それは、あなたがアニメインフルエンザに過度に働くために得られるものです。シェリルは彼女が雨の中で目立たなかったことに感謝しなければならない。それが彼女を即座に殺しただろう。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;反乱ゼントラディ司令官はおそらく、シェリルを連れてくるための究極の言い訳をしているにすぎないことが判明しました。彼は反抗する言い訳を探していただけだった。シェリルが病気になっているのは、他のゼントラディと一緒に行こうとする言い訳に過ぎない。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;アリルトはシェリルのグループのほかのメンバーと一緒にキャプチャされ、異なるゼントラディ派の間で緊張の対立が起こる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;シェリルのアルトへの言葉は謝罪の言葉です。彼女は最高の誕生日プレゼントを贈りたいと思っていたので、ガリア4に招待していた。再び何度も示されてきたように、アルトの夢は自由に飛ぶことです。明らかにアルトと恋をしているシェリルは、彼女にその夢を与えて彼女の愛を示したかった。シェリルがアルトと一緒にもっと時間を過ごしたかったので、シェリルがそのオファーを使用した可能性もあります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;反乱ゼントラディ指導者が行った演説は、第33海軍艦隊に関するクンの警告が正確であることを明らかにする。指導者は、人類に対する憤りと、ゼントラディが元のやり方に戻って戦争をもう一度やり直すべきかどうかについて語ります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;グレースがゼントラディ反乱軍司令官と協力しているという啓示もあります。アルトが捕虜を逃れたという情報がゼントラディに与えられたので、私たちはその恵みを伝えることができます。グレースはそれを知っていて司令官に伝えた唯一の人だ。明らかにすべてが計画通りに進んでいます。これは、レオンも関与していることを意味し、これはすべて彼の計画にも従っているということです。彼らはこの反乱が起きたかった。どのような目的のために、私はまだ知りません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これは、なぜシェリルが病気にもかかわらず、行かせられた理由を説明します。それはすべて計画の一部だった。それは、Zentradiの多くが反抗的なリーダーとチームを組むことを決定する必要があったという触媒を提供した。国連政府は彼らを気にしていなかったので、彼らは反抗すべきだという証拠だった。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Zentradiの反対側の軍隊の間で銃撃戦が起こる。しかし、すべてが可能な限り最良の方法で中断されます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ヤックのデカルト！名前：見て、空に！それは鳥です！それは飛行機だ！それは&amp;hellip;実際には飛行機です。しかし、重要な部分は飛行機の中にあるものです。彼女の音楽で救助に来たのはランカだ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これはもう一つの重要なポイントです。 Lucaの家族の会社はFold Faultsを通過できるFoldエンジンを開発しています。ちょうど私達がVajra船がしばらく後で見たのと同じように。私はこれがレオンの邪悪な計画に何らかの形で反映されているのだろうかと思います。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;とにかく、ランカのデビューコンサートは、バサラを引っ張り、ゼントラディに「私の曲を聴く」と効果的に伝えています。彼女は実際にはかなり良い仕事をしています。新しいスターレットが到着し、彼らは彼女の歌うデビューを見ることに興奮しています。いくつかのことは変わることはありません。そして、彼らのすべての戦闘行動のために、Zentradiはいつも大規模なアイドルオタクでした。だから私は彼らが人間と共通するものだと思う。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;しかし反乱軍の指導者はアイドルオタクではなく、代わりに戦い続けることに決めました。アルトとゼントラディの間の戦いは、それが最後のエピソードとアルトの俳優との会話にもたらしたパラレルのために主に面白いです。俳優は彼が彼の中に俳優の血を持っていたことをアルトに語っていた。したがって、アルトは俳優をやめることができませんでした。 Zentradiの反政府勢力は、Zentradiが戦争を行うという単一の目的のために作られたという点で、同じことを主張している。戦争は彼らの血にある。彼らは誰ですか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これまでのエントリーで、Zentradiの間でこの議論を見てきました。私はそれがこのシリーズで今後重要になると思う。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;しかし、アルトは、この議論に対して正しい人物ではありません。俳優がそれを作ったときに彼はそれを買っていなかったし、今買っていない。彼はあなたの遺産があなたの運命だとは思わない。結局のところ、彼は歌舞伎の俳優だった。彼はパイロットになり、飛ぶことを選んだ。他の人が同じことをすることができないと彼が信じる理由はない。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;この戦いはまた、むしろ不吉なものを予言する。海で何か悪いことが潜んでいる。私はそれが何であるかはわかりませんが、戦いが終わると、そのヒントが見えます。そして、LeonとGraceは、Gallia 4のこのイベントがそのために行われることを望んでいた可能性があります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;戦いが終わった後、彼らは素敵なシーンを一緒に持っているので、AltoはRankaと再会する。 Rankaは、彼女の緊張にもかかわらず、今日は勇敢だった。それが終わったとき、彼女の膝は、彼女がどれほど緊張していたので、やっと状況が終わったのだから、ついに消えます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;アルトは空を飛ぶ機会を得る。そして彼は後部座席のRankaと一緒に歌を歌います。それはとても素晴らしいシーンです。これは、アルトとランカが一度も持っていなかった1対1のシーンです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;一方、シェリルは、このエピソードの失敗のためにダウンしているようだ。 Rankaはその日を救った人でした。そしてRankaは、終わりにAltoと一緒にいなければならなかった人でした。私たちはポジションが、愛三角の最後のエピソードであった場所から逆転しているのを見ます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;もちろん、エピソードは最後の捻じれがなくても終わらない。海の邪悪なことはランカの歌に反応し、アルトのバルキリーを崩壊させるようなことをしているようだ。クラッシュサイトでは、おそらくアルトとランカは、おそらく最も目に見えない光景を見ています。マクロスのように見える。元のシリーズと同じように、オリジナルのマクロス。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は何が起こっているのか分かりません。私はそれがオリジナルのマクロスだとは思わない。どのようにそれができますか？それがオリジナルのマクロスであることは意味をなさないでしょう。もちろん、それは他に何ができるのか、それがなぜ元のマクロスのように見えるのかという疑問を生じさせます。それが何であれ、私は次のエピソードが私達にもっと教えてくれると確信しています。そして、私はまた、これもレオンとグレースの悪い計画の一部であると確信しています。今は、ほとんどすべてがそうであるように感じます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;サイドノート：ランカの周りについている緑のエイリアンリスが何であるかは誰も知らない。どこから来たのか、それがどこから来たのかは誰にも分かりません。しかし、それはランカをかなり忠実に守っています。その起源が実際に重要かどうかは疑問です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はこのエピソードのEDが「あなたは恋を覚えていますか？」と気に入っています。このリビューでこれまでに聞いたことのある他の曲も、そのフランチャイズ全体で私の好きな曲です。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はずっと思っていました。「なんと偉大なエピソード！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;Rankaマイケル、 &amp;ldquo;サウンドブースター&amp;rdquo;とすべてで来る！それが最高でした！その曲は素晴らしかったし、アルトは病気の動きを割引カムジンに引っ張った。深刻な技術を披露してくれたLucaのおかげで、（そしてNanaseに同梱されている！）&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;シェリルは彼女からすべてのものを取った - アルト、彼女が彼に与えたい誕生日のプレゼントを歌うチャンス&amp;hellip;私は彼女のために悪い感じ、彼女は病気になったように見える、そうでなければグレース/レオンの計画は、 &amp;ldquo;引き金&amp;rdquo;。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;それは大変だった、アイモは今惑星の踊り、ネコの歌、私は本当にそれが好きです&amp;hellip;アルトのバルキリーはバードマンのことで &amp;ldquo;EMP&amp;rsquo;d&amp;rdquo;を取得します。そのマクロス、そこに、たわごとに震えた！そしてランカは元のシリーズから最高の歌を歌います。私は本当に彼女の声が好きです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;リワッチャーはこちら：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;グレースとレオンのスキームは、シェリル（そしてアルト）がガリア4に到着すると、より明らかになりました。昨日、待っているゼントラディがシェリルの最高の聴衆ではないかもしれないと暗示されました。しかし、シェリルが最初に招待した理由は、ゼントラディ艦隊の司令官が、兵士の派閥内に進行中の不満を和らげるために文化を必要としたためです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;しかし、Sherylがあまりにも病気で演奏することさえ明らかになったらすぐに、休戦はすぐに崩壊する。そして、悪化する反乱派閥を率いるカムジン・エクスプレスは実際にそれを期待しており、反乱を公然とするためにその状況を偽証として使う可能性が高い。しかし、もちろん、彼は外部からの支援なしにこれをしたことはないでしょう。計画の一部にはSherylと会社を人質として雇うことが含まれていた。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;オープンな反乱のニュースは、SMSが大胆な救助計画を思い付く時期に、フロンティアに達しました。しかしLucaが理論上はVajraと同じようにフォールドフォルトに対してうまくいくプロトタイプのブースターにアクセスできない場合はうまくいきませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼女の健康状態が悪いにもかかわらず、シェリルがガリアに来る意欲を聞いた後、アルトは彼女の捕虜に挑戦する何かを考え出しません。それは彼と彼のための終わりだったかもしれないが、マイケルは戦いを中断する健全なブースターでちょうど時間に到着する。そして、初期のBasaraとは異なり、ランカのパフォーマンスは実際にはZentradiが望んでいたものでした。そしてこれは、即興のコンサートでZentradiの残りの部分が魅了されるように、急速に中断します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;カムジンexpyは例外です。しかし、アルトは、彼の遺産とアルトが彼の遺産を無視していると主張しているゼントラディの反政府勢力の指導者と並行して、華麗な使用で望んでいたことを巧みに味わう。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ほとんどの場合、通常の状態に戻って、マイケルはランタを帰郷させるためにアルトを軽く叩きます。また別のひねりで、Sherylの空の贈り物をAltoに分かち合うのはRankaです。残念ながら、この短い平和の瞬間はすぐに中断され、アルトは強制的に土地を崩壊させます。そして、彼らはGalia 4の別の秘密を発見します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;最後のメモ：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼らはそれらのキャラクターデザインでSDFMのノスタルジアにかなり力を入れています。私はなぜそれが人の性格を埋めるのを助けることなのか分かりません。名前は無名と呼ばれようとしていましたが、名前がないかどうかはわかりません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;だから交渉が崩れた。奇妙なフレーズのビット、しかし何でも。私が話したかった主なものはランカが直面する可能性のある罰だった。強制的なコミュニティサービス。ああ、恐怖はない！ジョークを除いて、彼らが超厳格で、彼女のアイドルスケジュールに干渉するならば、彼女にとっては悪いことかもしれません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;リレーは良いです、私は彼らがタイムリーにそこに情報を戻す方法を考えていました。幸いにも彼らはまた、シリーズが導入したまったく新しい挑戦を克服する真新しいエンジンを持っています。私は少し苦情がありますが、実際にはショーではなく、単なる傾向です。苦情は技術が少し劇的に改善しているということです。このような技術の点検はありません。新しいエンジンのコストはいくらですか？それはあらゆる方法で古いものよりも優れていますか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私は、アルトは何を正確に計画していたのでしょうか？彼の飛行機が始動するのにどれくらい時間がかかりますか？ここでは、Valkyrieがバッテリ/コンデンサなどで30秒間瞬時に動作する、緊急起動モードのアイデアがありますが、そのモードから通常の動作に移行することができず、起動に時間がかかります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ああ、私はアルトが土地を墜落させたことを完全に忘れていました。そして、マクロスのクラス船があります。理由はあると思いますが、なぜですか？私はこれを予期していることを覚えておらず、大きなフォローアップも覚えていません。私はそれがちょうど次の少数のエピソードに限定されるかもしれないと思うが。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;もう一度 &amp;ldquo;もう一度覚えていますか？&amp;rdquo;と聞いていいですね。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】弱虫ペダル GLORY LINE 6</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_yowamushi_pedal_glory_line_episode_6</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilers_yowamushi_pedal_glory_line_episode_6</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3kvr/spoilers_yowamushi_pedal_glory_line_episode_6/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3kvr/spoilers_yowamushi_pedal_glory_line_episode_6/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃スポイラー内&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これがソースマテリアルコーナーです！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントに返信して、今後のスポイラーについて議論したり、今週のエピソードを元のエピソードと比較したり、原材料について話したりするだけです。元のソースを見たことがない場合は、ここにスポイラーがあることに注意してください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このコメントの外にあるソースの議論は削除され、このコメントに向けられます。反復犯罪は禁止につながる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;＃警告する&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;mdash;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;第2シーズン以来の最優秀エピソードだが、今泉は箱根とのチームミスを認めてくれるはずだと思う。金城と小野田の交流のあいだ、私は喜びの涙を浮かべる準備ができました。ソククの中中力が登場して2日目を見るのを待つことはできません。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このエピソードは、私が最後のエピソードについて嫌ったものを補うものです。次のものを楽しみにしています！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ソフォクの授賞式+チームミーティングを開催することになった。私はペーシングがポストデイのエピソードの平均だったと言いたい。私たちは御堂筋をまったく見かけることはできませんでしたが、それがポイントだったと思います。笑。大野田は牧島が見守っていると聞いてスーパーサイヤンに向かうと間違いなくハイライトを出しました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼らが会合を持っていたのはかなり面白かったし、Kaburagiはちょうど地面に半分を敷いていた。だからこれは黒田のために進めているかもしれないが、おそらく外に出ていますが、ソホクのメンバーの一部もまた脱落するでしょう。おそらく二日目の終わりまでに、より多くのメンバーがDNFになるでしょう。新海の弟が何をすることができるのか楽しみにしています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ええと、私はCRが〜5：00（「Abs！We&amp;rsquo;re up！」）でラインと何をしようとしていたのか本当に分かりません。これはおそらく日本語で言い訳になるはずですが、アップは「アップ」という意味ではありません。これは、この文脈では「先導」のようなものです。また、「abs」と「up」は英語では韻を踏むことはありません。だから基本的に彼らは意味が間違っていて、英語でも馬鹿にしませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;カトマンさんは箱根のためにもう競争しないでしょうか？彼はレースを終了しなかったので。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;なぜこれが今シーズンの最高のエピソードだったのか知っています。それは小野田特集です。我々はそれが必要です。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>【アニメ海外反応】鋼の錬金術師 FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST 12</title>
      <link>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilersrewatch_fma_brotherhood_episode_12</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 08:24:56 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anime.syui.cf/2018/02/13/spoilersrewatch_fma_brotherhood_episode_12</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;引用元 : &lt;a href=&#34;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3k6v/spoilersrewatch_fma_brotherhood_episode_12/&#34;&gt;https://reddit.com/r/anime/comments/7x3k6v/spoilersrewatch_fma_brotherhood_episode_12/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;最初のタイマー。先生に会う時間。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;この最後のシーンでは、特に昨日のエピソードからのWinryのラインと組み合わせると、ショーのメッセージが大きくて鮮明になります。感じるのは大丈夫です。それにもかかわらず、特に深刻なものではないが、それは私が苦労するものであり、確かに私は西洋世界の多くの男性だと確信している。私たちは、幼い頃から上唇を堅くするように言われています。私たちは男らしい人でなければなりません。感情や脆弱性を示すことはできません。ストイックで頭を下げ、嵐を晴らすのは私たちの仕事です。そのようなジェノステレオタイプが日本でどのように認識されているかについて私は個人的に話すことはできませんが、確かに西側の流行の考え方です。そして、荒川はそれを少なくとも意識していたようだ.EdとAlはまったく同じように行動するからだ。怒りやストイックな自信の他に、私たちが本当にエモーションを見たのは、エドが愚かで自分自身を犠牲にして叫んでいたときだけだった。しかし、そのすべてが先生からの抱擁で変わります。先生は障壁を少し壊し、自分自身が感情的になることを許します。私はこれが今後大きなテーマになるとは思っていませんが、ショーが徹底的に探求しようとしているのですが、私の感情を表現し、自分自身を脆弱にすることを学ぶことが本当の闘いであったため、 。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はそれ以外のことはあまりありません。私はそれが私と共鳴したので、ちょっと話したかっただけです。明日お会いしましょう！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/UO9Emud.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Ah, the classic sink or swim survival training.&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/M0PZTgu.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;DAD?!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/8IjusZS.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;How long are they gonna keep up this charade?&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;それはシドだ！私はシドが大好きです。ここで彼はArmstrongに会うことを望んでいる&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;泉とシドはここでもっと恋人だ。 IIRC in FMA &amp;lsquo;03彼らの愛は、老夫婦のように、よりストイックに見えました。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼女の死んだ赤ん坊を変身させようとしている和泉は、そんなに私を責める。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;FMA &amp;lsquo;03と比較して、ここで男の子たちが何をしたかを知ったとき、いずみの描写とはまったく異なっていた。ここで彼女は男の子が何をしたのか理解したとき、彼女は理解しやすく、優しいものでした。 FMA &amp;lsquo;03では、彼女は寒くて、男の子たちはもっと叱った​​。個人的に私はこのラインのためBrotherhoodのバージョンがより好きです：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;私たちはどちらも役に立たないと思う。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;彼女はすぐに男の子達を理解し共感しました。そして、彼女は彼らの体に起こったことのために彼らがしたことを後悔していることを知っていたので、男の子を叱ることはしなかった。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - あなたが少しずつもっと成長したように見える。 -  Pfft。この線は本当に面白いです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - 初めて何年もあなたの生徒を見て、その中の1人を顔で蹴って、もう1人を裏返しにします。クラシック、古典的な和泉。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - スモールエドとスモールアルはあまりにもかわいいです。そのフラッシュバックの部分は特にマンガにはありませんでしたが、再びBrotherhoodはフラッシュバックやものを整理していますので、かなりうまくいきます。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - 男の子が赤ちゃんのことを話し始めると、SigがIzumiに与える一見、ああ男。 Ouchie ouch私の気持ち。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - 漫画は、子供たちの話題が和泉とのやりとりのテーマであることをより明白にしている -  [FMA]（/ s &amp;ldquo;エズは子供を産んだことはないと述べ、メイソンのお尻は大声でエドとアルに彼らが錬金術で何をしてきたかを実証します。もちろん、Brotherhoodには存在しないメイソンと共に、このシーンをカットしなければなりませんでした」。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - マンガは、フラッシュバックの開始前にはるかに多くのコンテンツを持っています。いくつかは、前の箇条書きで述べたカットシーンに結びついています。そして、それは非常に残念ながらカットされます。エドとアルが錬金術のデモンストレーションをするとき、エドは拍手をかける錬金術を使っていて、泉が「それを見たか」と尋ねる。実際に話す前に、子供たちは、彼女は欲しいように錬金術を使いませんが、もう一人の子供が死んだ猫を連れて来て、泉に抱きついてもらうように頼んでいます。彼女は猫を修理することはできませんが、彼女は彼女のために墓を作ることができます。 &amp;ldquo;）その最後のシーンはFMA 2003で間違いなく、Brotherhoodから切り離されたのは恐ろしいことです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - 私は本当にブラザーフッドがフラッシュバックの部分に戻って、泉の笑いのために病気をする傾向があることは嫌いです。漫画では、彼女が川でその壁をつないだ後、[FMA]（/ s &amp;ldquo;Resemboolの人々は実際に彼女の内部を医者が見ているように見せているが、国家錬金術師だと思っているが、エドとアルが彼女に先生になるよう頼んでいるのはここにあり、親がいないと分かっている無作為の男ではなくピナコ出身です。彼女は実際に見習いをするかどうかを決める」&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; -  Brotherhoodは、若いEdとAlを連れて帰ることを決めた後、IzumiとSigの列車でDublithに戻って柔らかい瞬間を切ります。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; -  [FMA]（/ s &amp;ldquo;Mason&amp;rdquo;）の存在を切り捨てた結果、Brotherhoodの島では、自然の中で生き残ってきた少年たちのことしかない。これは漫画の中でどのように行ったのだろうか（それとも2003年か）、[FMA]（/ s &amp;ldquo;Masonはマスクを着用し、島に住んでいる&amp;rdquo;モンスター &amp;ldquo;のふりをした男の子の食べ物を盗んだり、彼らと戦ったりするのは、彼らが戦うためにどのように教えられているか、「誰もがすべてであり、すべてが1である」という意味の意味である。代わりに彼はある種の昆虫を食べようとするアリを見ました。彼はその昆虫のようだと思っていて、偽装されたメーソンはアリのようでした」。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - ああ、誰かが、彼女がブリッグス山脈で1ヶ月間訓練したと言ったときに、泉が何を言っているかを正確に知りたいなら、第3の兄弟姉妹OVA、The Teale of Teacherをチェックしてください。 SIGとIzumiが最初に会った（非常に面白い）方法を備えています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;イズミは漫画の中で人間の変奏のものをもっと怒らせるが、イズミはエドとアルをそっと触れている瞬間だ。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt; - 漫画には、自分の失敗した人間の変奏についての説明はありません。彼女は臓器が取られていると言いますが、それはそれについてです。これは、[FMA]（/ s &amp;ldquo;Sig自身が、いずみが彼らの弟子であることから彼らを追い出した後、彼らが列車の駅まで歩いている間に物語を伝える人だからです&amp;rdquo;）。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://i.imgur.com/k8vNDIZ.png&#34; alt=&#34;Here it is!&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://vignette.wikia.nocookie.net/animevice/images/3/3c/Fullmetal_Alchemist_Brotherhood_Ep_12_Eyecatch_01.png/revision/latest/scale-to-width-down/640?cb=20151112072501&#34; alt=&#34;…&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ここは、第1裁判所の私の好きなエピソードです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;ホーエンハイムは、彼が去る前にエドを与える石の冷たい外観はとてもうまくいきます。 [FMA：B Spoilers]（/ s &amp;ldquo;彼らがその場面でエピソードを始めるという事実は、この物語がいかにしっかりと書かれているかをはっきりと明らかにしている。彼の息子たちの前で泣くのを恐れ、トリシャはそれには残念ではないと彼に言いましたが、勇敢な顔をして泣かないようにするために、彼は彼に嫌わしい印象を与えます。涙を隠そうとした&amp;hellip;そして、このエピソードはどうやって終わるの？イズミはエジプトとアルと、トリシャがホーエンハイムに言ったことと全く同じことを話していた。すべての単一の細部がいかによく考えられているかを気にしてください。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;[愛を感じて]（&lt;a href=&#34;https://78.media.tumblr.com/cf5c49e6bf2a50f38167306a661f073b/tumblr_mf4p78khPr1s0txgzo2_500.gif）&#34;&gt;https://78.media.tumblr.com/cf5c49e6bf2a50f38167306a661f073b/tumblr_mf4p78khPr1s0txgzo2_500.gif）&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;エピソードの終わり近くにエドとイズミの戦いは短いが、本当にうまくアニメ化されている。どのくらいカメラが動くのが大好きです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt; 「ナー、結局私は自分でやりました。それほど大きな問題ではありませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt; 「あなたは馬鹿だよ、傷つけるのは大丈夫だよ」&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;そしてそれがあります。ショーの2倍は、エドが本当に秘密をどのように感じていたのかを指摘しています。彼は彼が彼の体のために彼を非難した場合、彼は彼が自宅に瓶詰めを残して感じる方法を維持していたという事実を共有することはできませんでした。 Winryが言ったように、もしEdが彼に起こる悪い事を泣かせなければ、誰がそうするのだろう？このことを大声で言うのはよかったですか？エドは彼の人生のようになっていた。エピソード2に戻って、彼はウィリーに叫んだ。彼は確かに、彼のお母さんが死んでいるという事実を泣いているわけではない。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;このシーンでの音楽は、Brotherhoodのお気に入りの曲で、このエピソードと同じタイトルの「One is All、All is One」（&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CUF7jOM8Mp8）というタイトルです。私は誓い、それは私の好きなシーンの半分で再生されます。&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CUF7jOM8Mp8）というタイトルです。私は誓い、それは私の好きなシーンの半分で再生されます。&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;死亡した赤ちゃんといえば、このエピソードをすぐに持ってきて、赤ちゃんが生まれているというエピソードはとても理にかなっています。 Edが最後のエピソードを言ったように、錬金術師たちも赤ちゃんの作り方を理解することはできません。ほとんど彼はすぐに彼自身の錬金術の先生がレッスンの手を学んだことをすぐに知ることができることを知りませんでした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;エドとアルは私たちの意味を理解することは、「すべてが、すべてが1つです」も素晴らしい瞬間です。私は、物語が電源システムだけでなく、電源システムの背後にある何らかの意味を強調しようとするとき、いつもそれが好きです。 [FMA：B OVA Spoilers]（/ s &amp;ldquo;そして、それは基本的にすべてが馬鹿馬鹿しくなっていることを知っている。本当に、私は彼女が自分の「トレーニング」を思い出しているので、答えを笑ったと思う。エドとアルは彼女と同じ結論に達するだろう」&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はあまりにも忙しいために後ろにカップルであるので、エピソードへの反応で実際にはありません。しかし私は、私の友人（実際に私にこのショーを4年前に見せてもらった友人）が入れ墨を最近持っていることを分かりたかった。私はそれが意味するものでそれを呼び出すことができますが、それはおそらくスポイラーです。だから私はショーのこれまでのところ羨望、欲望、貪食で見たマークだと言いたい。入れ墨の芸術家は絶対に彼の最初の入れ墨であるように、私の友人のために素晴らしい設計を釘付けにした。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;私はママTrishaにこれらのフラッシュバックと感情的になる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;和泉さんのタトゥーは、何かを参考にする必要があります。それは何ですか？迅速なGoogle検索では、それはフラメルだと言います。 FMAウィキアから：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;「Flamel」とは、蛇や蛇がドレープされた十字架のような神秘的な記号と錬金術記号のことです。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;（古代ギリシャの薬のサイン）、カドゥケス（アルケミーの神に関連した古代ギリシアのシンボル、ローマのギリシアのシンボル）など、多くの古代のシンボルとよく似ています。エルメス）とNehushtan（悪魔の勝利を意味するヘブライのサイン）。中世のフランスの錬金術師であるニコラス・フラメル（Nicolas Flamel）のシンボルでもあります。十字架はフラメルの墓のイラストに現れ、多くはフラメールと哲学者の石の関係を象徴すると言います。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;gt;アルケミーでは、Flamelは、水銀のエリキシルと治癒プロセスの作成に関連して、錬金術術のプロセスにおける重要なステップである「揮発性物質の固定」を表します。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;いずみは私の好きなキャラクターのもので、ストーリーとバックグラウンドで大きな役割を果たしています。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;それはthoを抱きしめる。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;これらは9時から予定通りにリンクされていないのですか？&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;reddit-comment&#34;&gt;redditの反応&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;IzumiがBAMFであること以外に何を話し合うべきか分かりません。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>